Welcome to the Velvet Room.
With your new bond, you have awakened to the Star Arcana.
Now then, your story is drawing toward its climax.
As such, I imagine several surprises are laying in wait for you.
Your fate is at a crossroads.
If you fail to solve the mystery, your future may close before you.
No matter how thick the fog may appear, there is but one truth.
Defeat isn't the only thing that can bring your story to an end.
You would do well to remember that.
Find him?
Yeah.
That's definitely him. He's that way.
Rise, you have a better nose than I do!
You're still wearing that thing?
I feel more at home when I wear it on this side.
Why are you so beary dense?!!
What's this? A game?
He said, "Catch me if you can," so he probably thinks of this as a game.
Now I'm pissed!
I sentence him to a kick in the face!
That creep from the Midnight Channel is in here, isn't he?
How dare he mumble a challenge with those beady fish eyes?
The prick pisses me off!
Anyway, let's get a move on.
Aim for the ending.
All dudes like games!
And all the ladies like Teddie. Bear-sona!
Booyah!
I've always wanted to do that.
Did I look awesome?
Oh my, oh my! Coming from bear-hind's a cowardly thing to do!
Take this!
Will Teddie be okay on his own?
I think he'll be fine.
So, Chie and I were talking and...
Oh, no, no, no!
We think that guy who showed up on Midnight Channel might be the killer.
We were thinking the same thing.
Whadduya mean?
The suspect is a high school boy.
Take this!
And this!
After he killed King Moron, the police caught on to his trail.
Not to mention the Midnight Channel last night.
To top it off, his "catch me if you can" sounded awfully suspicious.
That guy came by my shop once.
I was selling tofu when he came up to me and started talking.
I think he was ranting about how biker gangs can't do anything unless they're in a group.
But I'm not in a gang!
He came up to Yukiko once, too.
He was by our school gate and called out, "Yukiko!"
Whoa, it's all coming together.
So he escaped to the TV world when he realized the cops were after him?
Makes sense.
But there's still so much we don't know, like why he targeted people who were shown on TV.
We'll have to ask him personally.
Yeah! We're finally gonna get our guy!
We just have to catch him!
Yeah!
We just gotta catch him!
He's as good as ours.
Are we done getting together like this?
Huh? Everyone's gone?
Did they leave us bear-hind?
They're pretty heartless!
Wouldn't you agree, Master?
Oh my, my! Master?
What's with that?
Wh-Who are you?!
I am nothing, and you are me.
Shut up!
Isn't this the killer's voice?
It was me! I did it!
Say something!
I feel nothing.
Look, over there!
No one even suspected it was me.
That's why I did the third one in!
I killed him, you hear?!
I don't care what an imposter like you has to say!
Get out of my sight!
You won't accept me, will you?
I am a Shadow...
Damn, this just had to happen!
Come to me.
I shall put an end to your emptiness.
Listen, listen, listen!
I wanna go to Yuki's house!
Parties! Traditional rooms! Hot springs! Yukata! Geisha! Mt. Fuji!
Th-That sounds like fun, but today isn't the best day.
It's tourist season since it's summer and all.
So we can't?
Maybe later.
Hey, why don't we go to Narukami's place instead?
Oh, I wanna go see his house!
We can let Nanako in on the fun.
Yeah, I'm sure she'd be delighted.
In that case, why don't we make her a feast?
Oh, are you guys good at cooking?
S-Sure... I guess?
Did you seriously forget about the whole school camping fiasco?
Hey, I'm good at cooking, too!
I'd like to cook for you!
Think you can best me?
Ta-da!
I just thought of a bear-y wonderful idea!
We could have a cook off with rice omelets!
Is that foie gras?!
It's an absolute must if you want a special rice omelet.
It certainly seems special.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
So the contest is between you and the three girls?
Yeah, and Nanako will be the judge.
Since I'm bound to win, the contest is just for show, right?
Ku-Kujikawa, enjoy boasting while you still can.
I'll finish you in one blow.
Whoa, looks like the sparks are already flying!
Huh? Come to think of it, where's Teddie?
Miss, you're beautiful.
I'd like to try some.
I want you to cook some of that meat for me.
Oh, but I'd get in trouble! I can't!
What's he doing?
Huh? Where's Amagi?
Well, Yukiko's family suddenly called asking for help, so she had to rush back home.
What?! For real?
We should save the celebration party for later.
Yeah, that'd be for the best.
So our cook off is canceled, too?
And here I wanted to bond with everyone!
So where'd these rice omelets come from?
Yu made all of them.
That's why he's the master!
Can we start eating, Big Bro?
Yeah, eat up before it gets cold.
Well then, I'll just help myself!
Let's dig in!
Wow, this is good!
Yeah, bear-y good indeed!
It's about average.
Yeah, it's average.
Geez, you're talented! Seriously!
You cool with this?
Yu, it's just average, so the party's not picking up like it should.
I put wasabi in one of them.
Ru-Russian roulette with rice omelets?!
Dude! What would you do if you served it to Nanako?!
I'm okay.
Raise your hand if you got a spicy one.
Huh? Maybe they didn't notice...
Yeah, well, this party's missing its zing.
We may have had to postpone our celebration party, but man, the case is actually closed.
Yeah, we caught the culprit.
We've been through a lot, but now we can get back to our normal lives.
I want to forget all that icky stuff quick.
I should go back to my world.
We're all going our separate ways.
No, let's meet up again.
Yeah, sounds good.
Yeah, we just gotta meet up again!
Yeah!
Sounds great!
What happened with the case after that?
I haven't heard anything since Kubo was caught.
You'd think everyone forgot about the case with the way no one mentions it anymore.
I'm sorry. The celebration party keeps getting postponed because of me.
It's okay. It's not your fault.
Everyone else has been busy, too.
I've got my hands full with my job, too.
I should be going.
Gotta run.
Yeah, see ya later!
Later!
Her inn must be busy.
It's great that everything's back to normal.
We never did get to go anywhere during summer vacation.
Yeah, that's too bad.
Let's go to the beach together next year. Sound good, Narukami?
Hey, Satonaka!
Oh, I'm sorry. That's right!
Yu, you won't be here next year, will you?
Right.
Oh yeah, about our summer homework...
Dude, is this legit?
So the rumors that she'd moved were true...
Did Rise say anything to you?
No, nothing at all.
She hadn't been coming to our group meetings lately, so I thought something might've been up.
The number you have dialed is currently not in service.
Women sure are scary!
I can't believe she took off without telling us.
I'm sure she had her reasons.
No, it just goes to show we were the only ones who thought we were friends.
Let's go!
We keep meeting over those murders, but there's nothing to talk about.
Is that so?
Sometimes, I think talking and trying to be all nice is exhausting.
You're like a couple that's grown bored with each other.
Moron, I was seriously asking for advice here!
What the hell?!
Sorry, my bad.
There they are!
What are they doing?
Studying for exams, of course.
Narukami, aren't you gonna borrow Amagi's notes?
Let's hurry on over.
But...
What? Something bothering you?
I'll pass.
You're such a weirdo.
Hey!
Big Bro...
No one comes over anymore.
Wouldn't it be nice if they dropped by to play sometime?
No one's coming over?
Guess not.
Sorry, man, but I have to work.
What do you think Teddie's up to?
Huh?
Don't you want to go back inside the TV?
I'm done with that crap.
More importantly, we should seriously start thinking about college and stuff.
What are you gonna do about entrance exams and stuff?
I haven't decided.
Are you gonna be okay?
Shouldn't you start thinking about that now for when you go back to your old school?
Well, I have to get back to work. Later!
Why?!
I have nothing.
Is that a Shadow?
Everything is "nothing."
What's it doing here?
Friendship is an illusion.
You are alone.
You are empty.
Persona!
M-My Arcana!
You have no bonds.
Persona!
You have nothing at all.
You're just like me.
Stop it... You're wrong!
I can't go on.
Yu! Yu!
Give me your hand!
That's right.
I am...
Yu!
Yu!!
Are you okay?
Thank you, Yosuke.
Narukami!
You're back!
Master, welcome back!
Thank goodness you're okay.
Hey, you all right?
Yeah. Let's get him.
Persona!
Not again!
You can't hit the Shadow until you destroy its outer shell.
Sweet! There he is!
He's rebuilding his defenses!
Oh no!
Dammit!
Not on my watch!
There! Now's your chance!
Go for it!
Please, Narukami!
Hit him nice and hard!
You're up, Master!
I'll let you take the spotlight!
I...
am not empty!
Makami!
King Frost!
High Pixie!
Pyro Jack!
Eight-Forked Serpent!
How many Personas does he have?!
Leanan Sidhe!
Rakshasa!
Ara Mitama!
Izanagi!
Who the hell are you guys?!
We're here to catch you.
The police are after you for killing King Moron on top of the other two murders.
Are you the one behind all these murders?
That's right! It was me!
I killed them all! It was me!
Huh? His Shadow vanished.
What's going on?
He's gone... the bastard...
It's all over now.
About Kubo...
I heard he confessed to everything, so all the cases are officially closed.
When asked why he did it, he said he wanted the attention.
That's horrible!
It's not like having a good reason would make it better, but you're right.
Let's leave the rest to the police.
Yeah, that's all we can do now.
Our job here is done.
My world will be peaceful once more.
We've sure been through a lot...
Like stud hunting. Bang!
Will you ever let that go?!
My Shadow did that, remember?!
So, what was it like for you, Yu?
Nothing happened.
Really?
Master really is one of a kind.
Oh, yeah. I guess we're done with our Personas, huh?
Do you think this will be our last time meeting up like this?
No, let's meet up again.
You bet we will!
It's summer break, so of course we will!
We're already pals.
Yay!
Hey, let's hold an afterparty.
Sounds good! We can celebrate solving the cases.
Let's go all-out and party!
This is amazing!
Let's dig in!
Let's start with the one Yukiko made.
What gives? It has no taste.
I feel like I bit into raw wheat gluten.
I-It's just too refined for you!
Your rice omelet is good.
Nanako!
Mine's up next.
W-Well?
This tastes awful!
It's good, too!
Nanako!
Oh yeah, totally.
This definitely tastes awful!
I thought you were gonna defend me!
Well, let's give Rise's a shot.
I just know mine has hers beat.
Yukiko!
Down in one blow!
I-It's a taste too sophisticated for kids!
Honestly, you're a bunch of kids!
It's spicy, but it's still good.
Nanako!
In the end, yours was definitely the best.
You mean Big Bro's?
It's really good!
I've never had a rice omelet like this before.
They were all good, but I like Big Bro's the best.
Really? Glad to hear.
It's about time I headed back to my side.
Are you going away somewhere?
Yeah, since they kept their promise.
Could you stay if you made a promise with me?
A promise with you?
Yep. Promise you'll come play with me!
Nana!
Pinky promise! If I lie, stick a thousand needles in my eye.
It's a pinky promise!
Say, Yu...
You know how the shopping district is holding a festival?
Whadya say we all go together?
Sure, that sounds good, Yosuke.
You just called my big brother Yu!
What? What? What's going on?
None of your business!
Come on! Tell me!
Give me some space!
But we're pals!
Don't use words you just learned!
Have you heard of New Feather Man?
I'm trailing him.
Teddie got on a bus.
You got a girl?
She's got a kid?!
Well, I'm off.
I'm the mysterious detective, Loveline!