Welcome to the Velvet Room.
Only those who are bound by a contract may enter here.
You have awakened to your power most brilliantly.
Please take this with you.
It is the Contractor's Key.
From this night forth, you are our guest in the Velvet Room.
Your Persona ability is that of the wild card.
Compared to that of others, it is very special.
It is like the number zero: Empty, yet holding infinite potential within itself.
I look forward to traveling the road of your destiny together
to see where your awakened power of the wild card will take you.
Satonaka!
Hey, Satonaka! Wake up!
Are you all right?
Where'd the monsters go?
They're gone for good.
Gone?
He's the one who killed them!
What? Really?
It was seriously amazing.
I heard you call it... "Persona," was it?
I don't really know.
Let's just get out of here before more of those things come.
Huh?
I'd love to, but...
How?
An exit?
We finally found you.
You seem like you know this place.
First, tell me what happened to the Shadows!
You mean those monsters back there?
Yes.
Yeah, right!
Did you provoke them?
Bear-ish the thought!
I've had it up to here with people barging in here and riling up the Shadows!
TVs?
Now off with you! Beat it!
I'm a busy bear!
Wait! What are you doing?!
H-Hey now!
Take it easy!
Ow...
Damn that bear.
We're back?
Thank God!
We made it!
Don't take advantage of the situation!
Hey, what's up?
This is the same poster I saw over there.
You're right. It's Hiiragi Misuzu.
She's been on the news a lot lately.
Her husband's the one who had the affair with the announcer that died.
Hey, wait a minute.
Hey, now. What about that freaky room?
She may be connected to the death of Ms. Yamano.
Don't go there!
I don't think my heart can take it!
Oh shit, I forgot! I gotta go to the bathroom!
This is giving me the chills.
I don't feel so good. I gotta go.
I went through hell yesterday.
What do you mean?
I'll tell you some other time, but you probably won't believe me.
Hey, you're Yukiko, right?
I've been waiting for a while now, Yukiko.
Who are you?
Let's hang out and have some fun.
Huh?
Stop it! You're scaring her!
Come on, Yukiko!
Where'd he come from?
The Amagi challenge ain't that easy.
Well, are you coming or not?
I'm not going.
Fine then!
Damn bitch.
Yo!
Good morning.
Oh, good morning.
That guy...
What did he want?
He was obviously asking you out on a date!
He was?
You couldn't tell?
You're so cruel, Amagi!
You did the same thing to me last year.
Really?
I don't remember that.
Wanna go out then?
No, I'd rather not.
I see.
Well, whatever.
My heart already belongs to someone else.
Konishi, right?
Yep.
Although, she hasn't texted me back since yesterday.
Huh?
Oh, man...
Did something happen again?
Hey, where's Amagi?
She left after her family called her.
They needed her help at the inn.
What inn?
Her family owns the nicest traditional inn in town.
And Yukiko is the heir.
What's up with her?
She still hasn't responded.
Can you hear me?
The principal has something to say, so pay attention.
Talking out of turn will earn you a spot on my shit list!
So pipe down!
I regret to inform you that I have a terrible announcement to make.
Konishi Saki of Class 3-B was found dead early this morning.
Huh?
Please remain calm.
I've been assured by the faculty that she wasn't the victim of bullying.
Her body was hung like Ms. Yamano's.
But it was a telephone pole this time.
Hanamura...
Hey, did you guys watch the Midnight Channel last night?
You wanna talk about that now?
Just hear me out!
Something was bothering me, so I watched it last night.
And I think I saw Konishi on it.
Don't you remember?
One of our classmates saw Ms. Yamano on the Midnight Channel and claimed she was his soul mate.
Yeah, I remember that.
And I heard that Konishi vanished before her death, just like Ms. Yamano.
That can't be a coincidence.
But...
Do you think people who show up on TV die?
Remember how we saw a poster of Hiiragi Misuzu over there?
You think the TV world is connected to the murders?
Konishi and Ms. Yamano may have gone in there at some point!
Hanamura, don't tell me...
Seriously, don't do it!
We were able to come back once, right?
If we go in from the same location, maybe we'll meet that bear again.
"Maybe" isn't good enough!
Okay, I'll go with you.
Seriously?
I could really use your help.
Satonaka, I'm leaving you in charge of this.
Wait! Are you being serious?
Don't worry so much.
So, are you ready?
Yeah.
Hey! Wait, I tell you!
I knew it!
This was never gonna work!
Now what?
Damn, that hurt!
Hey, it's you two again!
You came back?
It's the same place after all.
You two are bear-y suspicious.
Huh?
Lately, I can tell someone's been throwing people in here before the fog lifts.
The fog?
I know that if it's foggy on your side, the fog lifts here.
I do recall it being foggy on the days Ms. Yamano and Konishi died.
I don't think anyone forced you in here,
so you must be the one's throwing people in!
You two are the culprits!
You've gotta be kidding!
That's crazy!
Could it be...
that Konishi and Ms. Yamano were thrown into this world?
Obviously, you guys did it!
Just admit it!
What? How do we know you didn't do it?
Take off that stupid costume and show us your face!
Stop it!
Take it off!
Wh-What the hell?!
There's nothing inside.
It's empty! What's up with that?
Thank you bear-y much.
Narukami, does anything faze you?
Huh?
Okay, I'll believe that you guys aren't the culprits.
That was quick.
But I want you to find the real guy who did all this.
You have to stop him!
The culprit?
I just want to live here in peace.
Is this thing for real?
You're the only ones who can do this!
Do you promise?
Why do we have to?
Okay.
What?!
No way! You're going along with it?
Well, I feel sorry for him.
Yay!
You're being way too nice.
Okay, fine.
You better help us out then, stupid bear.
Wow! I can see so clearly with these on!
Hey, this looks like the shopping district.
I last saw a girl over here.
Hey, you dumb bear.
Is this the girl you're talking about?
That's her all right.
She disappeared into that store.
That's her family's place.
Do you hear that?
I wish Junes would go under.
Oh, I heard that Konishi's daughter is working there.
How could she, with her family's business suffering like it is?
What a troublesome child.
Who's that talking?
Shut the hell up!
Hanamura!
Saki, how many times do I have to tell you?
As the eldest daughter of the family who owns this liquor store, aren't you ashamed of yourself?
How dare you get a part-time job at Junes?!
Is that her dad's voice?
Why can we hear this?
Hey, is someone there?!
This is...
the ticket I gave her.
I never had the chance to say it...
Konishi?!
Hey! Is that you?!
Please! Where are you?!
I always wanted to tell Hana...
Huh? Me?
...that he was a real pain in the ass.
I was only nice to him because he was the store manager's son.
But he takes it completely the wrong way and gets all enthusiastic.
Pain in the ass?
Who cares about Junes, anyway?
The liquor store, the shopping district, my parents...
I wish everything would just disappear.
You're lying! This can't be!
There's no way she's like that!
It's so sad.
I feel so sorry for myself.
Actually, I'm the one who thinks everything's a pain in the ass!
Isn't that right, "me"?
Oh, my. Oh, my.
There are two Yosukes?
Who are you?
I'm you.
Me?
I know everything about you.
And coming here for Konishi's sake?
What a load of shit.
You just came because you thought it sounded like a good time!
What else is there to do out in this shithole?
That's not true.
If all went well, hey, maybe you could even be a hero.
And your sweetheart's death was the perfect excuse.
Who are you?!
What are you saying?!
I am a Shadow...
The true self...
I am your Shadow.
Fuck that! I don't know you!
That's right! Say it again!
You're not me!
Yeah, that's right. I'm me now.
I'm not you anymore, see?
That Shadow's getting bigger!
Persona!
Are you okay, Hanamura?
You're amazing, Master!
You really hit it hard!
No way!
He's nothing like me.
That thing came from you, though.
Bullshit!
You put on a good show of being carefree and happy-go-lucky...
'cause you're so terrified of being alone!
No!
You're not me! I don't know you!
He's attracting nearby Shadows!
Master, if we don't stop him soon, this'll get grizzly!
I know everything about you!
I know how pathetic you really are!
Let's ask Hanamura to do it.
The prince of Junes?
He thinks everyone depends on him because he's the manager's son.
What a loser!
You knew you were a nuisance,
but you played the part of the good guy well!
Shut the hell up!
Here it comes!
Booyah!
He takes it completely the wrong way and gets all enthusiastic.
You asked her out 'cause you're sick of living in the boonies!
You just wanted to do something fun!
You're wrong!
Shut up!
You're wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong!
Now disappear!
Izanagi!
Ow!
Oops. Wrong guy.
What gives?!
You loved her, didn't you?
Konishi, that is.
Yeah...
I truly loved her.
Then isn't that enough?
I guess you're right.
She dumped ya!
Shut up!
I knew it wasn't lying,
but I was so ashamed that I didn't want to admit it.
To get along with others,
I had to change the way I acted.
Even I think I'm annoying.
But my feelings for her were real.
That thing's a part of me, right?
When you get down to it, all of this is me.
No! Shut up, you brat!
There! Now's your chance!
Izanagi!
You're me...
And I'm you.
So this is my...
...Persona.
Narukami.
You really saved my ass.
Thanks, dude.
Ow...
That hurt...
You guys came back!
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?!
The rope got cut off, and I had no idea what to do!
The nerve of you guys! You're such morons!
I can't believe this! You guys suck!
I'm sorry, Satonaka.
Me too.
You owe me ten steaks.
Come again?
Okay, we accept your terms for forgiveness, right, Narukami?
Me too?
For you, it'll be beef bowls.
Sure...
I'll forgive you then.
I'm completely wiped out.
Same here.
Konishi and Ms. Yamano were thrown into that dangerous place.
The people who came in here were attacked by their Shadows,
just like Yosuke was a while ago.
If someone really did throw them in,
that's unforgivable.
We'll find the culprit and stop him!
We made a promise.
You did, anyway.
Hey...
I think that, with you, I can find the culprit
and solve the case.
Well...
I'll be counting on you.
Okay.
Is it true that you're the manager, even though you're still in high school?
No, I'm only filling in for my mother.
You're looking gorgeous in that kimono!
Huh? I don't know...
Is it true that Ms. Yamano stayed at your inn before she died?
Yes...
Dad's late again.
Oh, I need to do the dishes.
I'll help.
Okay!
Hanamura! Narukami!
What was that?
He bit me.
Good evening!
What? I don't get it.
See you tonight.
Don't come near me!
Don't look at me!