Welcome to the Velvet Room.
The Persona ability is the power to control one's heart,
and the heart is strengthened through bonds.
By becoming involved with others and forming bonds,
you were able to obtain the Magician Arcana.
Your power will grow as your bond deepens.
I strongly urge you to take this to heart.
Now then, I bid you farewell, until we meet again.
Glaciers of ideas, importing
To my friends, then exporting
To the next, keeping it open
We want no closing
Even without those, our thoughts can be duped
This mind trade no one can stop
An act of thinking is terrible to stop
We just wanna change it up, not drop
And my crew can rock it like uprock
Life is tedious if it ain't flowing
Copy and paste? Constant defaulting?
Put my courage to it
Begin showing off
That's the way we wanna live
Keep going, yeah!
What was so much of transparency
Turned into bright expectation
Instinct tells me to keep going together, going together
It's breathtaking moments in life
Addicted to it, minds craving more and more
I'm believing you and I can do anything
We can change the world
The sky's the limit, we can spread wings
to roadless travel, together we go
What's up?
He's cute! Is he yours?
I found him,
but my parents said to get rid of him.
He's going to be all alone again!
Hey!
I'm Satonaka Chie.
I'm Amagi Yukiko.
Nice to meetcha, Yukiko!
And you too!
Morning!
Good morning!
Did you see it?
Yeah, I did.
What's wrong, Satonaka?
Is Yukiko here?
Amagi? Nope, I haven't seen her.
Crap! What should I do?
Did something happen?
Last night, on the Midnight Channel...
Yeah, we were just talking about it.
I think I saw Yukiko on it.
I've seen her in that kimono before.
She wore it during that one interview.
I've been texting her, but she hasn't responded.
Tried calling?
It just goes straight to voicemail.
You don't think Amagi—
Don't even go there!
Sorry.
She's okay. She's probably just busy.
Or she could've lost her cell.
She might be busy helping at home.
Yeah! That's gotta be it!
I'm gonna drop by the inn!
You're leaving? But the bell's about to ring!
Yes?
Yukiko!
Thank God!
You're there!
Yeah, yeah! Okay.
Oh, it's nothing.
I'll text you later.
What a relief!
She's been busy 'cause a group came in without reservations.
But if it wasn't Amagi...
Who was on the Midnight Channel?
What's that?
Whoa, that handwriting sucks.
I took notes for Yukiko.
G-Gotcha...
Careful on the way down.
Hey! You the transfer student?
T-That's right.
Have you played much basketball?
No, not really.
Hey!
Let's go!
Tough luck, Ichijo.
We'll be waiting if you change your mind, new guy!
Even inexperienced sophomores are welcome!
It's really crowded today.
Hey, try sticking your hand in and calling him over.
W-What's wrong?
Something bit me.
I-It left bite marks! Are you okay?
It's making me cry.
No, it isn't.
Is that Chie I hear?
What's up? Is this a new game?
Teddie, does it feel like anyone's in there?
Who's "anyone"? I'm a lonely little bear like always.
This land feels so bear-ren.
Shut it!
So you're sure no one's there?
I-I'm not lying!
My nose is running as good as ever!
Someone showed up on the Midnight Channel yesterday, even though no one's there.
What's with that?
Let's check it out again tonight.
Good evening!
Tonight, I'm gonna score myself a hot stud!
Welcome to "Not a Dream, Not a Hoax"!
"Princess Yukiko's Hunt for Her Prince Charming"!
And I came prepared!
My lacy unmentionables are ready to go!
Just like my heart!
I'm out to catch a whole harem of only the best!
Well, here I go!
H-Hey, did you see that?!
I wish I'd taped it.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Where's your dad?
He left already.
He said he's gonna be late.
Are you going somewhere?
Y-Yeah, with my friends.
I'll be fine by myself. I can hold the fort.
High pressure is moving in,
so we should have clear skies all day.
Let's see what to expect for the—
It's gonna be sunny. I should do some laundry.
See you tonight.
See you later then.
Narukami!
Hey!
What kept you?
I found some stuff we can use in my closet.
Whatcha think?!
Hanamura, are those...
Of course, the blades are fake.
Which one strikes your fancy?
Uh...
Maybe both would be good too.
Two suspicious young males found,
one armed with multiple weapons.
Hey, hold it! No, no, no!
Are you resisting arrest?
We weren't doing anything! We aren't the bad guys!
We're just huge sword fanatics!
I'm not with him.
They're over there!
Sorry, excuse me!
Hey!
Wait!
Hanamura! Narukami!
What's going on here?
Yukiko's..
Courage
Average
Diligence
Callow
Understanding
Basic
Expression
Rough
Knowledge
Informed
A
Courage
Average
Diligence
Callow
Understanding
Basic
Expression
Rough
Knowledge
Informed
A
Come on, guys. Don't stir up trouble.
If you weren't Dojima's nephew and his friend, you wouldn't have gotten off so lightly.
I'm sorry.
Hanamura!
Huh?
Satonaka?
It's Yukiko.
Amagi?
She's gone missing!
She was definitely home last night.
But no one's seen her since then.
Actually, Amagi Yukiko's family asked us to help search for her.
Are you her friends?
Yes...
Did anything stick out as unusual?
Did Yukiko seem troubled?
Troubled?
Well, Ms. Yamano was staying at the Amagi Inn before the first murder.
It seems she had some harsh words for the manager.
And Yukiko's...
She's the manager's daughter,
so there's been some theories that she's laying low for some reason or another.
What the hell?!
You think Yukiko's the murderer?!
N-No, it's just a rumor floating—
Like hell it is!
Satonaka!
Calm down!
I-I'm not saying—
Hey, what's going on here?!
You implied Yukiko—
Let's go.
Come on, Satonaka.
Yukiko...
Yukiko is...
What did you say?
N-Nothing, really.
We've gotta save Yukiko.
Wasn't this?
Wasn't this on the Midnight Channel last night?
Satonaka, you should wait out here.
I'm going! I'm definitely going!
Once she's made up her mind, you can't stop her.
Teddie, is Amagi in there?
No doubt about it!
My nose is onto the scent!
Hey, don't run off on your own!
Damn it!
Don't leave me behind!
Yukiko! Yukiko!
She's really oblivious of her surroundings.
Hanamura!
Okay!
Persona!
Let's rumble, Persona!
Way to go, Master!
Jiraiya!
Yosuke, you've got a lot to learn.
Why don't I get any respect?!
Let's go!
Yukiko... Yukiko!
Huh?
Isn't this Yukiko's room?
She said red looks good on me.
Yukiko?
I hate the name Yukiko, meaning "snow child."
Snow is cold, and it melts quickly.
It's transient, worthless.
But it's perfect for me.
Yukiko, where are you?
I'm worthless.
Where are you?
Answer me, Yukiko!
Yukiko!
Still, Chie told me that red looks good on me.
Chie was the only one who gave my life meaning.
Chie is bright and strong, and she can do anything.
She has everything that I don't.
Compared to Chie, I'm...
Chie protects me.
She looks after my worthless life. Chie is so kind.
Yukiko, I...
"Chie is so kind," huh? What a joke.
W-What?
Is that me?
Who are you?
I'm Satonaka Chie.
What are you saying? I'm Satonaka Chie.
I'm also Satonaka Chie.
What's going on? This is crazy!
Yukiko said that I'm protecting her?
She said she's worthless!
You gotta love that.
What do you mean?
Yukiko's so good-looking, so feminine, so fair-skinned.
She's the one all the guys drool over.
When Yukiko looked at me with such jealousy...
Man, did I get a charge out of that.
Really, Yukiko can't do anything without me.
I'm the one...
I'm the one standing on top!
No! That's now how I feel at all!
You okay, Satonaka?
That's...
No, don't come near me!
Don't look at me!
N-No, this isn't me...
Satonaka!
Wait, stupid!
Shit! There are so many!
No, you're wrong...
So, you're just gonna turn your back and deny me again?
Shut up!
You're not... You're not...
Satonaka!
You're not me!
I am a Shadow... The true self...
Oh, no, no, no!
Satonaka!
Don't get in my way!
I see that you're gonna protect the "real" me.
Then you're gonna pay the price!
Master, you're the best!
Hanamura!
You're still here?
Just die already!
I'll be sure to take good care of Yukiko.
As my footstool, that is!
A stool?
Actually, I'm the one who can't do anything on my own.
I'm so pathetic.
But Yukiko depends on me.
That's why she's my friend.
I can't lose her!
No, I don't...
Satonaka, don't let her trick you!
Silence!
Hanamura!
I'm not trying to trick her.
These are my true colors.
My true colors, I say!
Yukiko's so pretty.
She's the one all the boys drool over.
They're me?
Yes, they represent how you really feel,
jealous and envious.
Without me around, she can't do anything.
She'd be nothing without me!
No... No!
No!
These are my true colors?
How horrible...
Who cares if they are?
You're still her friend, aren't you?
Yukiko!
They're right, Yukiko!
We're friends, aren't we?
You're the inner "me" that I pretended never existed.
You're the part of me I couldn't face.
But you're still me, aren't you?
Satonaka!
Cut the crap!
Are you seriously gonna acknowledge my existence and accept me?
Narukami!
D-Damn you!
I'm gonna tear you to pieces!
Hanamura!
Oh, dear! Yosuke!
You have established a new bond, allowing you to use another Arcana.
You possess the power to wield multiple Personas.
It is the wild card,
O Chosen One.
Chosen One?
Change!
Pyro Jack!
Oh, my! Oh, my!
N-No fair! He gets to use two Personas?
Get her!
Hanamura!
Yeah!
You're me...
What's this?
A Persona.
So this is my...
Yep.
This is my Persona...
Yeah, that's right. Yep.
He looks busy.
I'm so lame.
Yukiko could die the next time it gets foggy over here,
but I can't do anything about it.
I can't accept that.
You aren't lame.
I'm sure we'll need your help to save Amagi.
Thank you.
As a token of my gratitude, I'll show you something special.
What is it?
It's my dog.
He's a fatass and stinks like no other,
but he's the one who broke the ice and introduced me to Yukiko.
Yukiko.
No time to waste
but make you pace
It's okay to remove, copy, and paste
I'm doing my way
You do it your way
Don't just follow your left, find the right way
Stereotypes
Too many hypes,
But I'm the epitome of new types
Having the fear is power to my soul
'Cause I overcome them
That's how I roll
Expose your thoughts
Don't be afraid of making mistakes
Rules prevailing in
That may be your greatest rival
Believe in faith and your heart
Your true soul stop being in the shades
Come on, out in the open sun
Beauty of the child of destiny
Delightful days
are with rich density of love
Thorny path
There's no easy way for real bliss
So I keep on fighting for
Beauty of destiny
Chie!
Don't get in my way!
Let's go, partner!
Yeah, let's do it!
Was that from back then?
I won't run away.
I'm sick of these damn chains!