No! She can't be...
Dammit!
Dojima?
What's wrong, everyone?
Wait...
Is Nanako...
Crap! Dojima's headed for Namatame's room!
Namatame's room?
Oh, well, you see...
Hey, whadduya mean by that?!
Let go of me! I need to speak to him!
D-Dojima! Please calm down!
Why?!
Why did Nanako have to die?!
Give me back Nanako!
Dojima!
Give her back!
D-Dojima?!
Give her back to me!
Don't do this!
Why is he still alive when Nanako's dead?!
Dojima!
Why?!
I can't forgive Namatame either!
But, Dojima!
I'll kill him!
Uncle!
She's... She's all I have...
Dojima?
Quick, get him to his room!
Right away!
Come on, Dojima.
Hang in there.
I want to...
kill him myself!
Dojima...
Was he seriously gonna...
His only daughter's dead.
Nothing woulda surprised me.
First he killed Konishi,
and now Nanako!
Why? Why is he the one who gets to go on living?!
He tried to use the window!
You have your life, and now you want your freedom, too?
It's your fault that Nanako's...
I-I...
I...
12 o'clock...
Isn't this...
The Midnight Channel!
I failed to save her.
It's because you got in my way.
How? The real one's right here, and we already beat his Shadow!
The law can't touch me, anyway.
Is this how you truly feel?!
N-No!
I just...
To hell with the law.
I won't ever forgive what you did!
If the law can't touch you,
then we'll have to punish you ourselves.
Wait, Hanamura! What are you saying?
Do whatever you want.
You hate me, don't you?
I don't care either way.
Living or dying makes no difference to me.
But you can't.
You wouldn't dare, right?
Then I'll continue "saving" people.
It's my mission!
Whatever we want, huh?
Kanji!
Please move.
Don't do it!
This must be a luxury suite. Most hospital wards don't have such large televisions.
Naoto?
Why, with something like this in the room, this man could escape at any time.
Although once he enters,
he may find there's no way out.
No!
Wait a second!
You don't mean...
Are you serious?
We can't do that!
Are you just gonna turn your back and walk away?
That's not it! What's gotten into you guys?!
N-No, that's not how it is!
It's a misunderstanding!
Narukami!
Wait!
N-No!
How very unbecoming.
Wait!
Hanamura?
If any of you want no part in this, just leave the room.
Please don't!
Stop it!
I-I just wanted to save her!
So she wouldn't get killed!
Don't!
Narukami!
No!
The fuck?
Are you just gonna let him go, Yu?!
I can't do that!
This is our only chance!
At this rate, the guy's gonna get off the hook.
And then he'll go around "saving" people again!
We have to put an end to this ourselves!
That will make us no different than him!
We must...
reach out to the truth.
The truth?
Isn't this the truth?!
It's the reality right in front of you!
No...
Something's bothering me.
Well, what is it?
Maybe we're missing something.
Oh, come on!
Missing? Like what, exactly?
Enough of this bullshit!
Calm down, Yosuke.
The truth?
We should calm down and think rationally about this.
I realize now that we've heard almost nothing from Namatame's perspective.
How can we possibly understand someone who says killing people
is the same as "saving" them?!
Hanamura!
We all know how you feel,
but we've accomplished this much together, haven't we?
Yeah. So let's figure this out together, okay?
I'll think as hard as I can and try to help!
All right.
Let's go ahead and think this through as much as we need.
If we leave any unanswered questions behind,
we'd just be lying to ourselves.
To tell the truth,
there's something that's bothering me too.
Why did he start killing people in the first place?
Well, he said it was to "save" them, right?
That bastard's sick in the head.
After the first murder,
the police called in Namatame for questioning.
But everything in his testimony and his bearing...
No matter what they looked at, they found nothing suspicious.
Maybe he faked it real well.
Or maybe he started out with a normal motive and got a taste for killing after the first time.
If that were the case,
his motive for killing the announcer would be even more inexplicable.
Maybe his wife was getting suspicious, and she got in the way.
Namatame and his wife were separated at the time.
Hiiragi already knew about Ms. Yamano beforehand,
and Namatame was shocked to hear of Ms. Yamano's death.
So we have no convincing motive for Namatame to kill Yamano Mayumi.
Although, her name was written in Namatame's own diary.
Well, shit!
This is so confusing!
Teddie, don't just stand there and say—
Wha?
Huh?
Where's Teddie?
It's no use. He's not picking up.
Maybe he went home ahead of us?
I probably shouldn't call the house phone at this hour.
I'll make sure he's there when I go home.
Fog! Poison!
It's poisonous fog!
Run for it!
It's snowing.
It's freezing!
Hey, let's call it a day.
I'll be okay,
so thanks.
Yosuke,
let us know when you find Teddie, okay?
Sure thing.
Well, see ya tomorrow.
Let's go.
Oh, right.
Come on. You too.
I'm going to make snowmen with you when it snows!
Yeah! Let's make a big one.
Nanako...
Back then...
In his room, was it right to stop everyone from what they were about to do?
I...
Dammit!
Damn... it...
Where is this?
I'm sure I was in the hospital...
Nana!
What am I doing in such a lonely place?
What am I...?
I see... Now I remembear.
That was the deal, huh?
Guys...
Master...
What should I do?
I got to thinking last night...
If he "saves" people by killing them,
wouldn't he actually have failed to save us?
And another thing...
The Namatame who appeared on the Midnight Channel
said that he failed to save Nanako.
Well, maybe he really was trying to save the victims
by putting them inside the TV.
But he still threw in Konishi and Ms. Yamano, right?
Or what,
you think someone else was involved?
The warning letter.
The warning letter?
I think I know what's been bothering me.
It's the letters I received.
I believe the first one said,
"Don't rescue anymore."
The second said,
"If you don't stop this time,
someone close will be put in and killed."
Huh? Isn't that kinda odd?
Would someone who thinks he's saving people by killing them write stuff like "don't rescue" or "kill"?
Yeah, and the "will be put in and killed" part doesn't make sense either.
If the killer was writing it, wouldn't it be more like, "I'll put in and kill"?
You think someone else wrote it?
Other than the Kubo incident, we were all convinced there was only one culprit.
In Namatame's parlance,
"failing" would've been the first two cases, when the victims died.
Warning letters?
What are you talking about?
So it wasn't him.
We've all come here to find out...
the truth.
Please tell us everything you can.
You're willing to listen to my story?
We're the only ones who can fully understand what you have to say.
All right.
I'll tell you everything.
I returned to my parents' house, as if to run away from the scandal surrounding my affair.
Onto our next story...
City council secretary Namatame Taro's affair with TV announcer Yamano Mayumi has been exposed.
I hadn't been able to reach Mayumi at all.
For several days, the—
Wh-What the?
M-Mayumi?
Mayumi!
Now for our next story...
So, I'm sure you were expecting this,
A corpse was found hanging from an antenna.
but you're fired.
According to the preliminary police investigation and from her belongings and clothing,
she has been identified as local TV announcer Ms. Yamano Mayumi.
I thought the Midnight Channel was just an urban legend.
But...
Could that have been an SOS from Mayumi?
So I desperately kept watching.
And then...
Isn't that girl from the liquor shop?
After agonizing over it,
I decided to meet her
and told her to be careful.
But...
...she didn't take me seriously.
Pick up!
Please!
I knew she was gonna be murdered,
but I couldn't save her.
It was mortifying.
That's when I made up my mind.
I could hide her somewhere no one,
not even the killer,
could find her.
Are you trying to tell me it's safe over there?
Is that it?
So I thought, no matter what kind of place it might be,
it's better than being slaughtered.
Once things calmed down, I could just let her out again.
Even if I explained the situation to the victims, they wouldn't understand.
In that case...
I'll just take them away.
I thought my job as a deliveryman would be the perfect cover for my mission.
I did call the police, but they didn't believe me.
I thought I was the only one who could help them.
When I went after that little girl and entered the TV myself...
For the first time, I had doubts about myself.
I never knew you couldn't even get out of that place on your own.
You really were trying to save people, weren't you?
I secretly believed myself to be a hero.
I guess from your point of view,
people did stop dying once you started "saving" people.
The more you did it,
the more you really believed you were preventing their deaths.
I'm... such a joke.
I remember now.
I don't...
I don't belong anywhere.
Goodbye, Master...
Guys...
Nana,
I'm sorry I couldn't do anything.
Farewell.
Farewell...
Uncle!
Yu...
Nanako!
Is it true? My eyes aren't playing tricks on me?
Fuck yeah. Miracles do happen!
Thank God! Oh, thank God!
Dammit, Teddie.
Where the hell is that dumb bear at an important time like this?
Coming up,
we have the weather forecast for Inaba.
The continual fog is beginning
to strongly impact people's mental health.
We strongly urge the residents of Inaba to remain calm.
Do not be alarmed.
You are fast asleep in the real world.
Now then...
Why don't we take a moment to look back on your journey?
It seems that you have friends who are willing to follow the same path as you through this dense fog.
The bonds you share with your friends have blessed you with the Judgment Arcana.
I envy you,
for you have forged so many bonds in such a short time.
The Empress Arcana as well.
It would seem we have a bond connecting us.
I shall confirm our direction.
The car will be parked here for a while.
It can be worth your while to take the time to stop and reflect.
The case on Kubo Mitsuo?
Why do you want to know?
Very well.
Here you go.
But it isn't raining today.
A gift... to celebrate your sister's recovery.
Thank you.
Here I go!
I walked around all day and didn't hear anything good.
To find facts that even the police overlooked would be difficult indeed,
now that over half a year has passed.
I need some fresh air.
Looks like Naoto's stumped, too.
Thank you for the meal.
Huh, Yu? Y-You what?!
N-No way!
You ate it all?! And so quickly?
It was a difficult battle.
Nice!
Where are you going?
To clear my head after eating.
It's freezing out here!
Then why don't you go back in?
Maybe this'll get my deductive muscles flexing.
Junes is invading! Everyone, run for it! Run!
What's happening to this place?
There must be someone in town...
Someone who meets all of the criteria for this case.
The killer must have a connection to both Konishi and Ms. Yamano...
as well as be in a position to observe our actions periodically to some extent.
Finally, it must be someone who could approach your house without arousing suspicion.
Someone who meets all the criteria...
Why isn't he here when we need him?
Someone else killed them.
Do you have any idea who that might be?
Wait, dammit!
Burn in Hell!
There's no running away from it.
Come on! Let's go!