Away on Business
I see you have obtained the
Hierophant Arcana and the
Justice Arcana. Congratulations.
-Margaret
Study
Hall
||
Maze
Movie
Room
|||
Rest
Stop
||
Group
Date
Café
|||||
Movie
Room
|||
Rest
Stop
|||
Group
Date
Cafe
|||||
Maze
||
Miss Yasogami Pageant
Entry
Satonaka Chie
Amagi Yukiko
Kujikawa Rise
Shirogane Naoto
Kashiwagi Noriko
Ohtani Hanako
Kujikawa Rise
Shirogane Naoto
Kashiwagi Noriko
Ohtani Hanako
Minutes Later
Nurse's Office
Yasogami High Miss Yasogami Pageant
The fallen angels of the night flutter down to Yasogami High!!
Entry
Tatsumi Kanji
Hanamura Yosuke
Entry
Narukami Yu
Satonaka Chie
Amagi Yukiko
Kujikawa Rise
Shirogane Naoto
Kashiwagi Noriko
Ohtani Hanako
Satonaka Chie
Amagi Yukiko
Kujikawa Rise
Shirogane Naoto
Kashiwagi Noriko
Ohtani Hanako
Group
Date
Café
Performing
Romeo,
Juliet
and Hamlet
Romeo,
Juliet
and Hamlet
Romeo,
Juliet
and Hamlet
Music Room
Stir-fry Noodles
Haunted House
THE Long-Nosed
Fortune-Teller's Manor
"MISS" PAGEANT
"Miss" Pageant
Calculating
Remaining
Risette's
Shocking
Retirement
as an Idol
Rise
Kujikawa
Quits! The Lead
Role Goes to
Mashita
Kanami
Miss Yasogami Pageant
Burning
up!
Calculating
Announce the Results
Symphonic Band Concert
Mashita Kanami Surrounded by Fans While Shooting in Inaba
Group Date Cafe
To Yu! From Rise!