Slim Body
20 Minutes Later
40 Minutes Later
Tofu
Pickled Rice bran Radish
Country pickled radish
Super Special
40% Off!
Marukyu Tofu
Slim Body
I committed all of the murders in Inaba.
I am the killer.
291 Rotten Tangerine: I can't believe Risette retired.
292 Rotten Criminal: I committed all of the murders in Inaba. I am the killer.
293 Rotten Tangerine: Yeah, sure. And I've reported you in.
294 Rotten Tangerine: Attention whore.
295 Rotten Tangerine: Let's discuss Risette's ass.
296 Rotten Tangerine: Risette's washed up. Kanami Mashita's going to be the new
333 Rotten Tangerine:
....... If you're the killer, you have to prove it
334 Rotten Tangerine:
....... Don't encourage 292. Let's turn him in.
335 Rotten Tangerine:
....... 292, quit blowing us off.
336 Rotten Criminal:
....... I'll prove it to you!!!!!!!!!!