Welcome to the Velvet Room.
How will you proceed now that things have taken a turn for the worse?
Do you believe in fortune telling?
This is the fate that awaits you.
What is this place?
It's so beautiful!
It's like a storybook vision of Heaven.
Mom, where are you?
Why'd you have to go?
Why'd you leave me behind?
Like Heaven, huh?
Nanako...
Look over there!
Nanako!
Namatame!
Fuckin' bastard!
You followed me here?!
Nanako!
Big Bro...
Are you Namatame Taro?
And you are?
Oh, you're the ones I saved!
Huh? This dude high or something?
What are you talking about?
I'm going to save this girl.
Fuck you!
Give Nanako back!
S-Stay back!
Wait!
Namatame Taro!
You put the people you saw on the Midnight Channel into this world.
Am I correct?
That's right.
What made you do that?
On rainy nights... on TV...
they signal me...
to save them...
Signal you?
If I hadn't put you in the TV,
how would you have ended up?
Huh?
Are you trying to say that we wouldn't have been able to face ourselves?
What?!
But we nearly died!
Yes.
Exactly.
This guy's completely lost it!
I just wanted to save you!
Screw you! "Save," my ass!
You're just killing people!
You're the murderers!
I know that you plan on killing this child.
What are you talking about?
I'll save her.
I'll save her, too!
Stop it!
I'm a savior!
A righteous hero!
Big Bro, I can't breathe...
Nanako!
What's going on?!
H-His power is attracting more and more Shadows to him!
I'm going...
to save her!
N-Nanako!
Nanako, I'm going to save you!
Nanako!
Don't be rash, please!
I will... I will save her!
Narukami?
Wait!
Something's not right.
Yu, what's the matter?
My body...
What? What's wrong?
Guys, run!
Dude, what's gotten into you?
Master!
The enemy is controlling him?
That's horrible!
Yu!
No, Yosuke!
Hanamura!
Shit! Who knew this guy would be such a pain in the ass?
This is bad!
That's—
You serious?
He's charging up
so he can take us out in one shot!
Dammit...
Stop it!
That's right. I won't let anyone get in my way.
I won't let anyone stop me!
Narukami!
Stop it...
Stop it!
Big Bro, don't fight with them.
Nanako...
Now's our chance!
Nanako!
Stay back!
Shit!
Big Bro...
Are you okay?
Give her back.
Give her back!
Oh shi—
My body is...
...moving...
...on its own!
I'm going...
to save that girl!
Dammit!
Yu, please save Nanako!
Please, run for it!
Kohryu?!
I can move again!
You did it!
Daddy...
Don't interfere!
I'm going to save her!
You've done enough!
Here's your chance!
Th-The Shadows are going bear-serk!
Rawr!
Nanako? Nanako!
Nanako, hang in there!
She's must be in pain, but she doesn't seem to be injured anywhere.
This place must not be good for her!
We need to carry her out, quick!
Yeah!
Nanako...
still hasn't recovered from her cold.
And then to go through that...
Nana's still so small,
so her other self didn't appear like it did for everyone else.
And she got caught in all that craziness.
All those Shadows just had to show up!
There's no way she could've handled that, dammit.
Why did I waste time
listening to what Namatame had to say?!
If I hadn't tried to engage him in conversation,
and we'd rescued Nanako immediately...
Naoto, it isn't your fault.
It is my fault!
Even then, I prioritized solving the case over Nanako's safety.
Because of that, Nanako is...
All right,
enough of this pity party.
Tatsumi?
Is feeling pathetic and consoling each other gonna solve anything?
We gotta believe in her.
Get it together, Naoto!
I'm sorry.
You're absolutely right.
Naoto...
Weren't you desperately trying to save Nanako?
Thank you.
I'm glad you were there.
Thank you...
Come on, guys. Acting all gloomy won't solve anything.
Think how Nanako would feel if she saw us like this.
Yeah, you're right.
Nanako's gonna be fine.
Let's believe in her.
Dang, you were pretty cool for once, Kanji.
Huh?
What's that supposed to mean?
Guys, don't make a scene in the hospital. Sheesh!
Seriously.
Isn't the fog especially thick today?
Yeah, and it's really cold, too.
What's up?
Check this out. It's about Namatame.
It looks like he regained consciousness this morning.
"According to the police interrogation,
he confessed that he regrets what he did and admits that he was just scared."
So he admitted to his crimes.
It's finally over.
At long last.
Oh, yeah.
I received word from the hospital this morning that it's okay to visit Nanako.
For real?
Then we should go see her when school lets out today!
It sounds like Nanako's doing a bit better.
Thank God.
Yeah, that's great news.
Oh, where's Naoto?
I was going to invite her too, but she wasn't in her classroom.
So this is where you went.
What're you doing here?
Oh...
So Nanako's doing better?
That's great.
Is there something on your mind?
Not really.
I'm just having a hard time believing that the case is truly over.
You would.
Is that a problem?
No, I'm impressed.
You would be.
Really?
Really!
You know, you're a unique person.
You referred to me as your friend, and...
Do you remember what you said at the hospital?
At the hospital?
"I'm glad you were there."
Isn't that what you said?
Yeah.
I just wanted someone to acknowledge me.
I wanted to be needed.
That's why I was trying so desperately to solve the case.
If you take away my ability as a detective, I have nothing.
But you said you were happy that I was there.
You gave me a place where I belong.
It made me really happy.
I see.
W-Well, I better go.
You're headed for the schoolyard.
W-Well, weren't we going to see Nanako?
Let's get going.
It's still just lunchtime.
Huh? Oh, y-you're right.
I'm really sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Big Bro!
Nanako!
Sorry. She isn't able to talk a lot yet.
Dojima, you came here again?!
Oh, well, you see...
I understand that you're worried about your daughter,
but you still need your rest, too!
S-Sorry...
I'm sorry. I'll wheel him back to his room immediately.
Hey! What do you think you're doing, Adachi?!
Hey, stop it!
Dojima, that's so lame!
Big Bro?
I'm right here.
Yeah, I'm so glad.
About Namatame...
He's still mentally unstable,
but we're slowly piecing together his story.
Anything new?
Well, this is still a secret,
but I guess it's okay to tell you guys.
There were entries about Ms. Yamano and Ms. Konishi in the diary we found.
Huh?
Looks like Namatame had been making advances on Ms. Konishi.
We think that could be connected to why he killed her.
That son of a bitch!
W-Well, I'm gonna go now.
Hanamura...
S-Sorry! I'm all right.
Don't bottle it in.
I-I'm not!
Namatame's been caught.
He can't hurt anyone now.
Yeah, you're right.
When do you think Nanako can go home?
Dojima's still hospitalized, too.
I wonder what's up with this fog.
I know a person whose child has been bedridden because of it.
I wonder if it's really poisonous.
Run! Evacuate immediately!
This is poisonous gas! It's loaded with viruses!
You'll die if you breathe this fog!
What's with him? What a creep.
The idea that this fog is poisonous is just plain stupid.
Although that was an extreme example,
Wouldn't you agree?
Yeah, you're right.
It's true that people are getting increasingly worried.
It's not just here, either.
People everywhere are talking about the fog.
It's very unusual for fog to last this long.
Visibility's so bad, it's kinda scary.
It's just like on the other side.
You mean in the TV?
G-Guys, put on your glasses!
Whoa, it's all clear.
What the...
Wh-What the hell's going on?
These glasses are meant to help us see through the fog in the other world.
But putting that aside, no glasses would improve one's visibility in a fog under normal circumstances.
Could the fog from over there be leaking into our world?
Huh? You guys think that's it?
I-It just popped into my head.
Could the fog from the TV world really be leaking into our world?
Is that even possible?
Here you go.
Thanks again.
It does seem a lot like the fog on the other side,
but beyond that, I'm clueless.
I see.
And the case against Namatame hasn't been going well, huh?
Right.
According to Adachi,
they haven't made any progress with Namatame's interrogations.
It seems he's still confined to his hospital bed,
so further interrogation has yet to commence.
The fog isn't leaving, and the interrogation isn't going anywhere.
We solved the case, but I still feel bummed out.
Hey...
Can I still stay here?
Huh? What brought that on?
You kept your promise to help me find the person who was disrupting the other side.
Oh, I guess we did.
So I should be going back,
but I don't wanna go until Nana gets better.
How many times do we have to say it?
Of course you can stay.
M-Master, are you sure?
Do you really mean it?
Yeah.
Then maybe I should move in with you, too!
Being together would really heat things up.
Now that you mention it, it has been unusually cold.
Oh, that's right!
So you promised Nanako?
Yeah, I promised that we'd go buy a space heater.
If we're getting a space heater, we'd better get some oranges to complete the set.
That sounds nice!
Kanji, what'd you buy?
Wait, what?
Is that wool?
I thought Nanako and I could make some knitted animals when she gets better,
so they're for that.
Kanji, you're so sweet!
Screw you!
I know!
While we're all here,
why don't we pick out a Christmas present for Nanako?
The space heater isn't good enough?
No!
All right, as soon as Nanako's out of the hospital,
how about we have a party at your place?
A party? That sounds nice.
Yes! And we'll bake the cake!
Of course!
Of co
urse!
Oh no you're not! Are you trying to send Nanako back to the hospital?
Of co
urse!
Yes, this is Narukami.
Y-Yu?
Yes?
K-Keep calm and hear me out.
There's been a sudden change in Nanako's condition.
Hurry over to the hospital!
Nanako...
Are you a family member?
Yes!
Right this way.
Nanako? Can you hear me?
Your big brother's here!
Big Bro...
where are you?
Here! I'm right here!
Big Bro?
Nanako!
Your dad will be here soon.
He's coming.
He'll be here soon!
Daddy...
Hang in there, Nanako!
I even looked at some space heaters.
Let's go buy one together, okay?
Remember our promise?
We're going to make snowmen when it snows.
We promised that we'd play together a lot.
We promised!
Big Bro...
We'll be together forever.
I'll stay with you forever!
I'm scared...
Big Bro...
Daddy...
I failed to save her.
How come he's the one who gets to live?!
Let's put an end to this ourselves!
Goodbye, everyone!
We must... reach out to the truth.