Welcome to the Velvet Room.
I foresee two Arcana shining brightly in your future-
The Moon and Strength.
Soon, you shall forge bonds that will give rise to even more new powers.
These bonds shall illuminate the path before you and be your eyes to see the truth.
Now then, please take care until we meet again.
Hey, let's go steady.
Give me your love.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Yo.
Thanks for your help yesterday.
Damn, I'm beat.
But we saved Amagi, so that's all that matters.
Where is she, anyway?
Yukiko's taking a few days off since she doesn't feel good.
But she said there's nothing to worry about.
Oh, that's good.
I feel much better now that Yukiko's back.
We can finally get back to our normal lives!
Man, you're already back to normal.
Huh?
We've been worn ragged these last few days, right, Narukami?
I'm just fine.
What? Just what are you guys made of?
I've been buying heat pads, guzzling health drinks, and exploiting Junes' massage chairs like crazy!
Actually, you're surprisingly tough.
Did you used to be in a club?
No, not really.
Oh, yeah!
If you haven't joined a club yet, I could use you for something.
Did you see Risette's commercial?
The hot one?
Ichijo!
Yeah.
Hey!
S-Satonaka!
Guys, take five!
So, uh, what's up?
I brought a new teammate!
For real? Oh, you're the new guy!
You actually came?
Satonaka asked me to. I'm here to watch.
I'm Ichijo Kou. Nice to meet you!
Um, likewise.
I'm Nagase from the soccer club.
This is the soccer club?
Nope! I'm just ditching practice to goof off here.
Ichijo and I go way back.
Aren't you helping with practice since they're short on members?
Yeah.
We're about to go under 'cause we lack serious players,
so we'd love a new recruit!
Well, I'm not so sure.
Please!
Help us out! Just for a while!
I'm begging you!
Uh...
He's our temp, Narukami, so go easy on him!
Go on and say something.
It's a pleasure.
H-Hi!
So, where's everone else?
They left.
We wanted to work on our rebounds, but they said it's too tiring and left.
Not again...
Oh, yeah. This is our manager, Ebihara Ai.
I rarely show up.
Huh?
So don't ask me for any favors, okay?
I'm outta here.
But we still have to clean up!
Later!
Hey, we're gonna head on out.
There's a party tonight, so...
Hey! Are you serious?!
Gotta run!
Later!
Bye!
I'm back!
Oh, he's home!
Hello!
Hey there.
We got off work at the same time, so I brought him along.
I'm Adachi Tohru, the guy who's been your dad's slave since spring.
Hey, isn't it great that Amagi turned up?
But she isn't off the hook yet.
Ms. Amagi says she doesn't remember anything that happened while she was missing.
It sounds pretty fishy, like she's hiding something.
Stop blabbering, dumbass!
S-Sorry.
The missing person's case has settled down,
so I'll get to take a hard-earned break during Golden Week.
Really?!
Yeah, you wanna go somewhere?
You've got at least one day open, right?
Yeah, I think.
Let's pack our own lunches!
Sounds good. We've been eating enough processed food as it is.
But I can't make them.
That's what he's here for!
Right?
Huh?
Okay, I'll entrust you with making our lunches.
Uh, I'll do what I can.
I wanna go to Junes!
Well, if it isn't the new recruit.
You're... Ebi?
What was that? I'm Ebi-hara Ai.
Hey, wanna ditch morning classes with me?
The team wanted me to get some stuff they need, so give me a hand.
You really oughta!
It's so nice to have someone carry my stuff.
I can get anything I want.
The basketball club has some unique needs.
That was obviously a lie!
Figures.
This feels great!
Everyone is still at school studying their asses off.
That's what makes this fun!
It might be nice sometimes.
Wow. So you get it!
And here I thought you'd be a stick-in-the-mud.
It's my first time ditching class.
Is that so?
What are you doing?
No way! You made that from a napkin?
You're different than the other guys.
I might actually like you.
I'll play with you again sometime.
But next time, it'll be after school, okay?
Nice pass! You're looking good.
Is our manager a no-show?
She's the only reason I come.
You know, she's probably busy guy hunting after school.
She's super loose!
I hear she's got a sugar daddy.
Oh, me too!
Not surprising with that face, that body, and that ass!
Of course she's gonna have a sugar—
Knock it off.
It's not nice to make up crap about her!
But this is seriously the—
Hey, uh...
Oh, shit!
She probably heard us!
She just gave us the death stare. What now?
Hey...
Huh?
Are you okay?
It's no big. They're always like that.
I'm fine.
Actually, I'm flattered!
My heart's racing! What should I do?
I totally got the hots...
for Ichijo.
I see.
He's cheerful and kind, and he even defended me!
You think he has a girlfriend?
Dunno.
Please help me out! I need you to ask him what his type is.
Me? Why?
You just gotta! You're the only one I can count on!
I see.
Do I like anyone? Why are you bringing this up?
So you don't?
Geez, you're really open about this.
Don't tell a soul!
Sure.
I-It's Satonaka.
W-What's your problem?
I'm so jealous that you get to sit next to her!
Now that you know, you've gotta help me out.
Later!
I'm gonna kill myself!
Take it easy!
I know Satonaka! She's that frumpy girl, right?
I'm a hundred times better-looking!
You need to calm down!
Don't touch me!
I'll kill myself if you get any closer!
Your parents would be really hurt.
He rejected me, didn't he?
Even though I became cute...
I worked so hard to become cute.
But what's the point if he doesn't love me?
I know how you feel.
I used to be fat and clumsy, so everyone bullied me all the time.
They used to surround me and call me "gross" or "Piggy-hara."
I decided I'd show them and went on a diet.
I read magazines like they were textbooks to learn the secret to being popular.
I see. So you worked hard for this.
But it wasn't enough.
I thought I was cute, but nobody loves me.
What gives?
Please stop crying.
You've worked so hard. I'm sure you'll find a boyfriend eventually.
You're so nice to me.
Huh?
I should've fallen in love with you.
Really?
Let's head back.
Hey, let's go steady!
You need to own up to what you said.
Until I can nab another guy, I want you to love me.
What?!
Otherwise, I'll kill myself.
Hey, Narukami!
Good morning!
Oh, good—
Yu!
Huh?!
Hey, Yu!
Let's skip school today and go hang out!
But, uh...
Isn't that the transfer student?
Is he going out with Ebihara Ai?
When did they hook up?
I said I wanted caramel sauce!
Oh, sorry.
I won't forgive you until you say you love me.
Out with it, Yu.
I... I can't.
C'mon, let's kiss!
What?!
It's okay. Nobody's watching.
We are kinda like lovers, you know.
Cheese!
No, I can't! I can't!
How dare you rotten shitheads skip school?!
Narukami, we're meeting up at Junes's food court after school today.
We need to review the cases.
Yeah, we should.
Huh?
Not gonna get that?
Huh? Oh, right.
Hello...
Too slow!
I'm your girlfriend, so pick up within three rings!
What was that about?
Oh, nothing really.
No, I better call her back, or she'll really let me have it.
Hello.
Whatcha think about those two?
Who?
Narukami and Ebihara.
They're a cute couple.
Like hell they are!
They play hooky, and they're all over each other in public!
That's not like him at all!
Ebihara's got issues, I guess.
I can't believe he prioritized a date over reviewing the cases today!
What's the big deal, Satonaka?
Oh, don't tell me you're...
Now I get it!
Huh?
He's a cool dude, and he can use a bunch of Personas.
What?
Come on now.
You may be in some dire straits, but just leave everything to me!
You've lost me.
Guys, listen up!
We're holding a practice game this weekend.
We haven't had one in ages, so let's go all-out!
Okay...
Yo! Got a sec?
Oh, Hanamura!
What are you doing here?
Satonaka here wants to become your club's manager.
What?!
Can she give it a shot?
Yeah, y-you bet!
Is that why you dragged me here?
You gotta get your foot in the door if you're gonna beat Ebihara!
Say what?
Life's hard for a girl in love.
I totally don't get you!
Man, this is great! We could use the help with the upcoming game.
Well, I guess I can help with the game.
I think a certain someone's glaring at me.
Wow, the all-out battle for love has begun!
What are you trying to do?
Hey, Narukami.
Yeah?
I might quit after this upcoming game.
Why?
Well, my parents never approved of me being on the team.
I'm from a fairly big family, and I'm the heir and all.
I've only ever told Nagase about this, but I figured I could trust you.
I just want to win my last game.
Could you help us out?
Yeah, you bet!
Sweet! In that case...
I'll tell Satonaka my feelings for her if we win!
What?!
I just came to cheer 'em on,
so what am I doing in a uniform?
Sorry, man. We're short on players since there are some no-shows.
It's nothing new! Let's give it our all.
You're not welcome here, even as a temporary manager.
Well, I heard that you hardly even attend practice!
Life's hard for a ladies' man, don'tcha think, Narukami?
Huh?
Let's play fair!
Seeing you up close pisses me off even more.
I can't believe I lost to a frumpy girl like you!
Frumpy? And lost what?
I'm going through hell because of you!
I have something I'd like to say to you too.
It's horrible the way you push Narukami around.
What, you've got the hots for him?
He's my friend!
You're loved and have friends to boot.
You've got it all, you bitch!
What the hell?!
If you're Narukami's girlfriend, try to treat him better!
Ah, youth!
One minute left!
Damn hag!
Hey, knock it off!
This might be Ichijo's last game!
Just sit down and watch him!
Huh?
We did it!
Good job, guys!
One beef bowl!
Oh, over here!
Huh? Wait. Does your family run this place, Aika?
We're classmates, but I didn't even know!
Yep. Thanks for coming.
Here's our menu.
I'm always starving after a game.
Whoa, you do deliveries!
I'm digging right in!
We deliver anywhere.
Anywhere?!
It's good!
Really good!
Ichijo, I'm sorry.
Huh?
I let you down...
in your last game.
Oh, that?
I changed my mind.
That game helped me realize something.
I really do love basketball.
I really hate losing, so I can't let it end like this.
We were only able to compete 'cause you joined.
I seriously owe you one, Narukami.
Thanks, man.
I wasn't much help, though.
And I'll tell her how I feel when we win someday!
Right.
So let's continue enjoying basketball together, okay?
Sure!
Sorry, but I don't seem to mix well with a certain someone.
Really?
Um, Ichijo...
Can I stick around with the basketball club?
Of course you can!
Man, my last shot was so awesome.
Did you see it?
Hey, Yu!
I already said I did!
What?
I would've covered for you if you missed.
I'll be okay on my own now.
Like that would ever happen!
I wanted you to baby me a little since you're so nice,
at least until I got over the shock of being rejected.
I thought maybe I could learn to love you.
You can have this as a memento.
It's a total pain, but I'm gonna try acting like a manager.
I came to that decision thanks to you.
Thanks a lot, Narukami!
Chie, aren't the stir-fried noodles yours?
Thank you!
Oh, this smells good.
You look a lot better, Amagi.
Yeah, sorry to have worried you.
Now that Amagi's back, we should resume our investigation.
And I'll help! I'm gonna teach whoever's throwing people in there a lesson!
Let me help.
I want to know who hates me enough to want to kill me.
Yeah, and the police are out of their league on this case.
But we have special abilities,
right, Narukami?
Yeah. We have to find the culprit.
Yep!
Right!
Oh, yeah. Aren't those about ready?
Yeah, you're right!
Let's dig in!
Gimme a bite! Just a bite!
Same here.
What do you think you're doing?!
My fried tofu...
He's chasing them!
We're just a loving couple passing by!
It has a funny picture on it!
So this is our special headquarters?
The next target is...
You're dead! So friggin' dead!