Welcome to the Velvet Room.
Today I think I'll tell you a story about a certain Persona.
It's the Persona Black Frost.
You see,
he lived alone for over thousands of years.
While enduring the solitude, he prayed to the sky, over and over.
Pleading, "Give me a friend."
Eventually, the god he served granted him one for a single day.
And the two of them frolicked through the fields, as happy as could be.
But when the sun set, his friend vanished.
Black Frost regretted his request,
for he never would've asked for a friend
if he had known he would've been left sad and lonely.
Hence Black Flo—
Black Flau—
I didn't mispronounce it.
Come on.
Let me alter your bodies already!
Here it comes!
I don't want wrinkles!
I'd rather die!
Oh, no, no!
Hmph!
Hey, Yu...
You've been so good to me, Yu.
Don't lose heart!
I feel as though we've been friends for decades.
That's just your imagination.
It feels like just yesterday we entered the TV looking for Naoto.
That was today, not yesterday!
No!
Uh-oh!
Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no...
Wh-What the heck?! He's getting shaggy!
Is that a mushroom?!
Ew! He smells like mold!
He's changing colors!
No way!
They're so useless.
Sorry for the wait.
Now then, let's begin the operation.
Don't forget about me!
Kanji!
Izanagi!
I see there's another annoying fly!
Narukami!
Yu!
It's gonna use that attack again.
Quickly, change Personas!
Arahabaki!
Next up is a fire attack!
Abaddon!
She's so fast!
Watch out!
A lightning attack's coming up next!
Mot!
Your attacks won't connect with her zooming around.
You need to slow her down first!
Oh, no! It didn't work!
Dammit!
My, my, you're so annoying!
Narukami!
No!
Yu, you're cool even when you're old!
Yu, you still up and kickin'?
I'm just getting started.
Mashter, I shink I'm forgetting shomething.
Try to remember.
Had enough?
Stop it.
Stop hurting these kids!
They have to sit still.
Otherwise, I can't fill their bodies with holes.
I was inept at making friends ever since I was little.
Even after my parents died in an accident and my grandfather took me in,
I never made any friends.
Grandfather would secretly let me help with his client's cases.
Before I knew it, people started calling me Junior Detective!
Now that it's come to this, I should fuse...
How do I fuse them again?
Mashter!
I wish we didn't have to get old!
At first, everyone went nuts over me.
But my status as a "child" was sufficient to offend many of those whom I worked with.
With time, I can become an adult!
But... But...
I can't do anything about being a girl!
That'll never change, even after I grow up!
That's why I'm going to give you a new life as my present to you.
Cut the crap, dammit!
I suck at making friends, too!
Big fuckin' deal!
I hate crude simpletons!
Oh, youth...
If only I could be young again.
Oh, I just remem-beared!
I can bear-come young again!
Why couldn't you have remembered that sooner?
It's rude to make your elders wait!
We're counting on you.
Let's get our youth back!
Use Energy Shower!
Re-energize!
That's what I'm talking about!
I feel so full of life!
Beelzebub!
What is that?
A fly?!
No way! It's huge!
You're one huge fly!
The damage you've inflicted has slowed her down big time!
She's gonna use that!
Everyone, run for it!
Teddie, get running!
Doing a barrel roll!
Rollin', rollin', rollin'!
You guys...
saw everything, huh?
Do you not like being a girl?
Is that why you always dress like a boy?
My sex doesn't fit my ideal image of a detective.
If they had the slightest "concrete" reason to look down on me,
no one would need me anymore.
You don't know that!
You must know already...
that what you yearn for isn't to become an adult...
or to become a boy.
Try facing yourself.
I...
I kept ignoring you,
pretending you didn't exist.
You've always been inside me.
I am you...
and you are me.
It's my dream to become a cool, hard-boiled detective someday.
What I should yearn for...
No, what I must strive for isn't to become a man.
It's to accept myself for who I really am.
You're a devious bunch.
I can't believe you kept something like this hidden for so long.
No wonder the perpetrator has eluded the police.
Hey!
You okay?
Sheesh, she really put her life on the line for this.
I never doubted...
that you'd all come for me.
What a dumbass.
You're no genius at all.
You're too damn reckless!
But...
Now we know.
The case isn't over yet.
Yeah, you've proven that to us.
I'm back.
Big Bro, welcome ba—
Welcome back!
Good evening.
Have you heard? They found Shirogane!
Y'know, the Detective Prince?
We attend the same school.
He went missing for days!
But apparently, they just found him.
Way to put a scare into everyone... Yeesh!
R-Really?
You don't seem very surprised.
You didn't already know that he'd been found...
did you?
No.
Oh, come on, Dojima!
You really oughtta do somethin' about that habit of yours.
Rumors spread fast out here, y'know.
But man...
Why'd he disappear?
Maybe he got sulky after being given the boot and ran away from home?
He was taken off the case?
Yeah.
But I tell you, I was shocked to hear that he up and vanished like that.
If there had been a fourth kidnapping and murder...
Adachi!
We still don't have any concrete evidence with that boy.
How are we gonna make a case like this?
I wonder if Dojima's instinct is right,
and maybe there really is—
How many times do I gotta say it?!
Quit running your mouth!
S-Sorry!
Now see here!
Don't worry about the case.
Just go study like a normal student...
If you don't...
Huh?
I'm going to bed.
Sorry, I killed the mood there.
It's fine.
But yeah, I can totally understand why Dojima's worried.
Just leave the case to us police.
It would suck if you got caught up in it, right?
Are more scary things going to happen?
Oh, sorry, my bad!
It'll be okay.
Nothing scary's gonna happen anymore.
Just leave it to me!
Believe it or not, I got the most brains in the whole police department!
Oh, was that too hard to understand?
Did you get it?
Yeah...
Well, good night!
What does "got brains" mean?
It means he's smart.
Huh...
So things'll be all right?
Yeah...
Man, midterms are starting next week!
Don't bring that up! It's a total buzzkill.
Naoto!
Good morning.
Have you fully recovered?
I have.
Thank you for the other day.
Don't sweat it.
But what's with that uniform?
After some thought,
I decided to stick with what I've been wearing.
Oh, it's the Detective Prince!
That's no prince! He's a she!
Uh, what?!
N-No way!
I'm kinda shocked, but also a little disappointed.
If that's a girl, then holy cow!
Goodness, rumors sure spread quickly.
Just ignore them.
That's right!
Actually, I was hoping I could discuss the case with you.
Sure. We did leave things hanging since the incident.
Someone lurking in this town is behind all of these kidnappings and murders.
Let's go into this later.
This is awesome!
My old lady couldn't make this if she tried!
The vichyssoise you made just recently was amazing, too.
You're the best!
Um, are you even listening to me?
I want more! But I don't want to finish it all.
I'm sorry.
Hey, listen to what Naoto has to say!
So you were at home when you got kidnapped, right?
It started when my doorbell rang.
But when I opened the front door, I saw no one there.
Just as alarm bells sounded in my mind,
someone grabbed me roughly from behind
and covered my mouth with something.
Immediately afterward,
I was put into something like a sack and carried on someone's shoulder.
Wow, how could you remember all that?
I was psychologically prepared for it.
You're too damn calm about all this.
Judging by their actions and body type, I'd say the culprit is definitely a man.
I heard no conversations or voices,
so I believe he is acting alone.
I see...
After that,
I felt a single impact,
which I assume is when I was thrown inside the TV, but...
Huh? What's up?
But the time from kidnapping to that point seemed too short.
About how long did this take?
Once he caught me,
it was over in a few minutes.
So he threw you in the TV right after catching you?
There is no question that the culprit is the same in each case.
Then what about that Kubo guy who killed Mr. Morooka?
That was a copycat killing.
But the question remains, though, as to how he learned of the world inside the TV.
That's it! That's what was bothering me.
What do you mean?
Kubo could enter the TV, right?
Then why didn't he kill King Moron the same way?
I believe he didn't understand the other world as well as the true culprit.
Even though I can now enter it myself, it wouldn't occur to me to use it for murder.
That makes sense.
But Kubo's criminal act did verify one thing.
What's that?
The killer isn't retrieving the bodies and hanging them upside-down.
That is simply what happens to the corpse...
when someone is killed over there.
So he isn't trying to send some crazy message, huh?
If we could ask Kubo in person,
much of our speculation could be tested.
But man, if you were so calm, couldn't you have, uh...
I don't mean you needed to catch him, but you know?
T-To tell you the truth,
I was really...
Really what?
Scared.
Scared?
I'm sorry!
Of course she was scared!
She is a girl!
Oh, r-right.
Listening to you talk, that totally slipped my mind!
You got balls for a girl.
What?!
Wh-What makes you say that?!
A... girl...
A-Anyway,
this case is no longer just a job or someone else's affair.
I want to know the truth.
Please allow me to join your effort.
Of course.
It'd be reassuring if a famous detective teamed up with us.
Thank you.
Are you happy now, Kanji?
What?! I don't know!
I'm counting on you.
Huh? Uh, okay...
And ta-da! Here are your glasses, Naoto!
Th-Thanks.
Wow...
Teddie, I can sympathize with your drive to find yourself.
I'll try to help you in any way.
Wow, you're a sweetie pie!
May I flirt with you?
I won't cooperate with you on that one.
Oh, my, my, my, my, my!
Actually, I have a suggestion regarding Teddie.
Could you spend tomorrow after school with me?
You want a doctor to take a look at Teddie?
Right. I thought having a doctor take a look at him might be a good first step.
So why us?
There's that fog on the other side, not to mention our powers.
We should make sure that it isn't negatively affecting our bodies.
Everyone's results appear normal.
What about Teddie? Did you find out anything?
We certainly did.
We learned that we don't know anything.
I had them take an X-ray, but...
What gives?
It's so fuzzy!
I even had them retake it several times.
Was it wise to take that without getting permission first?
Naturally, I intend to return it...
discreetly.
Ta-da! Sorry to keep you waiting.
Aren't those...
They're the results to your physical exams!
It's too em-bear-rassing if I'm the only one who gets fully exposed.
It's time for some thrilling announcements!
Teddie, if you wanna announce something, start with the girls' three sizes!
Say what?! Are you a total moron?!
Let's see...
What is it?
Naoto, is this accurate?
What?
They didn't measure you incorrectly, did they?
Say what?! Which way should I interpret that?
Cool it, perv!
A-At any rate,
the doctors were unable to find any physical problems!
As such, we will no longer be needing this!
Wait! Let me take a peek!
Give it back!
N-No! Don't look!
Don't you want to find out?
Hey, Hanamura! No peeking!
A-About what?
Wait. Were those sizes legit?!
Naoto's bust size.
Wh-What the hell?!
I couldn't care less!
I see.
But dang, she's amazing.
Amazing?
You mean Naoto?
Women fight to be their own selves, even if their secrets get exposed.
True enough.
Watching Naoto has taught me something.
It's easy for me to act tough.
But when we went to save Naoto,
and I saw her accept herself and strive to be true to herself,
I thought she was pretty amazing.
So I've decided to be myself and help others understand me!
Keep it down at the hospital.
If you're wondering why I shared this with you...
I-It's because you saved my life, and you're my best bud!
Let's continue being friends.
What's up?
Good morning.
This was in my shoe locker.
The sender was...
a girl.
She even put down her grade and class number.
Going by the heart seal on the envelope, I doubt this is a commission.
So it's a love letter?
In other words, there's no reason to read it.
I am only interested in commissions for more cases.
I see.
In that case,
there is something I would like your help with after school.
I'll take the case.
Thanks again!
Here's our rainy day special.
No one has been able to discern everything that goes in the Mega Beef Bowl.
This will be a tough case.
You always manage to throw me off somehow.
When it comes to you,
everything's a big deal.
Whether it's the case
or a beef bowl.
Life is a series of big events.
Hm...
Beneath the meat is... more meat.
And more meat and more meat...
Is this based on some sort of set law?
I'm counting on you, Detective Prince.
A hit-and-run near Samegawa, huh?
He just can't get over it.
I said to keep out of this!
So you're running away from her again?
Do you think I'd go to Heaven if I died?
Please protect her!