Welcome to the Velvet Room.
Ah... It seems we have a guest with an intriguing destiny.
My name is Igor.
I'm pleased to make your acquaintance.
I shall accompany you on your journey.
My name is Margaret.
This place exists between dream and reality, mind and matter.
It is a room that only those who are bound by a "contract" may enter.
Perhaps such a fate awaits you in the near future.
I wish you the best until we meet again.
Narukami!
It's so quiet.
Thank you for riding with us.
We'll reach our final stop, Yasoinaba Station, momentarily.
Please prepare to exit.
Yasoinaba. Final stop, Yasoinaba.
There's nothing here.
Oh, here already?
You're more handsome than that picture let on!
Man, you've gotten big!
It feels like you were in diapers just yesterday!
Don't you remember me?
Oh, man...
I bet your mom already told you, but I'm her younger brother, Dojima Ryotaro.
And this is my daughter, Nanako.
Go on and say hi.
Hello...
What? Is he making you blush?
Ouch!
Ballad singer Hiiragi Misuzu's new husband,
Secretary of Inaba City Council, Namatame Taro, is under suspicion of adultery.
But damn, it sucks that you had to move because of your parents.
His mistress is allegedly the beautiful TV announcer, Yamano Mayumi.
Still, I'm looking forward to spending the year with you.
Uh... Yeah...
Huh?
I gotta use the potty.
Welcome!
Can you go alone?
Thanks a bunch!
Are you traveling somewhere?
No, I just finished picking my nephew up.
He's moving here from a city.
I see.
Fill it up with regular gasoline.
Thank you.
So you in high school?
Huh? Yeah...
We need some new part-timers. You interested?
I'll pass.
Does it surprise you how little there is to do here compared to the big city?
You'll get bored sick if you don't work or somethin'.
Just give it some thought.
Pleasure meeting you.
Yeah...
Well, I gotta get back to work.
Sorry for the wait.
Ready to go?
Are you okay?
Car sick? You don't look so good.
Nah, I'm fine.
You must be beat after the long trip.
Let's hurry home.
This is meant to be your welcome party.
But this was all I could put together.
Well, cheers.
So, we're going to be your family for a while.
Thank you for the food.
Consider this your home and make yourself comfy.
Yes.
Now then, let's have some sushi—
Geez, now of all times.
It's Dojima.
Yeah.
I see. I'm on my way.
Got it.
Sorry for the sudden change in plans, but feel free to help yourselves.
Dad!
I'm not sure when I'll be back.
Nanako, it's raining out!
What'd you do with the laundry?
I brought it in!
Cool. Well, I'm off!
He's a detective, right? Isn't that your dad's job?
Yep. It's always like this.
He leaves whenever the phone rings.
We'll have the weather report after these commercials.
Ah!
It's Customer Appreciation Day every day at Junes!
Come see and experience it!
Every day's great at your Junes!
Not eating?
Thank you for the food.
You've probably heard by now,
but Narukami's transferring to another school.
His parents have work abroad, so...
So I'm stuck here for an entire year, huh?
Do you wish to learn the truth?
Is this a dream?
Then try to catch it.
Who is that?
I better leave him alone.
All right, sit your asses down!
So here's the new transfer student.
This sad sack's been thrown from the big city out to the middle of nowhere like yesterday's garbage.
Go on. Introduce yourself!
I'm Narukami Yu.
Infidel!
You were eyeing that girl by the window, weren't you?!
That's it. Your name's going on my shit list!
See here. This ain't like your scum-filled—
Hey, Teach!
Huh?
May the transfer student sit here?
Sure.
Go sit down already!
We call him "King Moron." Isn't he terrible?
I guess.
Shuddup!
I'm starting homeroom!
Fog?
That's it for today.
It's back to the old grind tomorrow,
so come prepared!
I saw the Midnight Channel!
My soul mate is Ms. Yamano.
For real?!
Attention all students.
There's been an incident in the School Zone.
Please remain calm as you leave the campus.
I wonder what happened.
Talk about creepy!
I repeat: Attention all students.
Oh!
Narukami!
Huh?
There's been an incident in the School Zone.
Going home by yourself? Wanna walk with us?
Please remain calm as you leave the campus.
This is so freaky, huh?
Y-Yeah...
I'm Satonaka Chie, and this is Amagi Yukiko.
Sorry for troubling you.
Yukiko, don't apologize!
It makes me look like I got no upbringing.
I just wanted to talk to him a bit.
Hey there, Miss Satonaka!
Huh?
This was way cool!
Thanks! See ya!
Not so fast.
What the hell?! You cracked it!
My Trial of the Dragon!
I'm sorry. It was an accident.
I'll pay you back as soon as I get my next paycheck.
Are you okay?
Don't mind him, Yukiko!
Just forget about him. We're going home.
I better leave him alone.
So it's just for a year?
And it's because of your parents' work...
I thought it'd be something stickier than that.
Now, Chie! You're being rude.
Hey, Adachi!
How long are you gonna act like a rookie?
Ready to run back to HQ? Well?!
S-Sorry.
What a sight.
Someone help me!
You're a lifesaver!
Thanks, dude.
Narukami, right?
I'm Hanamura Yosuke.
Yeah. Nice to meet you.
So, do you know what this town's famous for?
Huh?
It's beefsteak. Beefsteak!
It sounds lame, but it fits right in around here.
I'll treat you since you helped me out.
Nah, it's cool.
It's no prob, dude!
Free later today? 'Course you are, since you're new here.
I went through the same thing.
You can count me in!
You better pay up to prove you're sorry.
Hey, what gives?!
This isn't beefsteak!
I can't afford two steaks.
I can't believe it!
And here I had my palate set for meat!
What's that supposed to mean?
Exactly what it sounds like!
The body found yesterday was identified as local TV announcer, 27-year-old Yamano Mayumi.
Whatever. Now quit complaining and eat it before it gets cold!
According to the Inaba PD...
Huh?
Wasn't this on the news yesterday?
It's freaky how that shit happened way out here.
What if the murderer's right under our noses?
Don't even! It's too creepy!
I'm just teasing.
Let's talk about something fun.
Oh, I know!
Have you heard about the Midnight Channel everyone's talking about?
The Midnight Channel?
Yeah, doesn't it come on if you watch TV alone at 12 AM on a rainy night?
Yup. And whoever appears on screen is your soul mate.
It's supposed to rain tonight. Wanna give it a shot?
I'm amazed that kiddy crap still grabs your attention.
Y-You think it's a joke?!
See? This is why you can't get a boyfr—
What was that?!
S-Sorry, I said too much!
You're sorry? You expect me to cut you some slack?!
It's Konishi!
Hey!
Oh, it's little Hana.
Hey there!
Hello.
Not feeling well?
Nah, I'm just a little tired.
That would be Konishi. Isn't she pretty?
Her family runs the liquor store in the shopping district.
I see.
Did you think she's his girlfriend?
It'd be nice if she was...
Apparently they're fellow workmates.
You there.
Are you the transfer student?
Uh, yeah.
He doesn't have many friends, so...
Oh, he's a really nice guy,
but you gotta let him know if he starts annoying you.
Oh, no, I couldn't.
That was a joke.
Come on. That wasn't funny!
Well, back to work I go.
Later!
Oh, hey! There's one more thing...
Oh, yeah. Sure.
We can discuss it during my next break.
Booyah!
Well, what's the big deal?
Oh, I see.
What went through your mind when you found her?
W-Well...
Did you see anyone who was acting suspicious?
No, not really.
So that's our interview with the girl who found the body.
The victim, Ms. Yamano, was suspected of having an affair with the City Council Secretary,
so this incident could have stemmed from relationship trouble.
Daddy's asleep!
But doesn't skewering her on a private antenna seem a bit over the top?
He was up all night again.
The police are still unsure if this was an accident or potentially murder.
He has to because of work.
At Junes, every day is Customer Appreciation Day!
Come see for yourself, and get in touch with our products!
Every day's great at your Junes!
I'll go take my bath.
Yeah, right...
I am thou...
Thou art I.
Ye who shalt open the door...
What the hell just happened?
What?!
You went into the TV?!
Yeah.
Satonaka and I just saw some weird shadow people.
Did you see anything?
You know, on that Midnight Channel we've been talking about.
Nuh-uh, I...
Sorry, but I have to go.
Busy helping out at home?
Yeah, sorry.
It's cool.
Hang in there!
Thanks!
Man, I know you were probably just dreaming,
but the part about not fitting into the TV because it was too small sounds pretty realistic.
So what would happen if he tried it on a bigger TV?
What?
Wanna try it out on one of the big TVs at Junes?
Or not!
We're seriously doing it?
Why not?
I've been wanting a new TV, anyway.
Could you use your connections to get me a better deal?
Hell no!
Huh?
Oh, I'm the manager's son.
I transferred in from Tokyo too.
It was about six months ago.
Is that so?
Junes makes life easier,
but now the shopping district seems so empty.
You shouldn't say that in front of me!
But I hate talking behind people's backs.
W-Well...
Isn't this...
Did you see anyone who was acting suspicious?
Huh?
Oh, I see.
She looks like Konishi, doesn't she?
No, not really.
Huh?!
Everyone in class is talking about it.
So that's our interview with the girl who found the body.
They think Konishi was the witness on the news.
The victim, Ms. Yamano, was suspected of...
For real?
That explains why she skipped school today.
She didn't text me back either.
Whoa!
Y-Your hand went right in!
So how's that trick work?!
A-Awesome!
I think I can go deeper.
Inside what?!
Oh, crap! You're gonna make me piss my pants!
You're gonna what?!
Oh, crap! Here they come!
People are coming! What should we do?!
Customers are coming, and I gotta pee!
We'll hide! Let's just hide for now!
C'mon, over here.
Hey, don't drag me!
Hey—
I'm gonna blow!
That hurt...
Ouch!
Where are we?
Inside the TV, I think.
No way!
Don't sound so calm while spouting nonsense!
Man, this hurts too much to not be real.
I busted my ass.
Nothing new there.
How'd we get in here, anyway?
I don't see an entrance anywhere!
I can't see anything with this fog.
Wh-Wh-What now?!
I dunno! Don't ask me.
I wanna go home right this second!
Yeah, but how?
Wh-What's that?!
At least it looks like we lost that weirdo.
Where are we?
What the hell?
This is messed up.
This poster...
What? What is it?!
My bladder's about to burst!
What? That's all?
You're peeing right here? Give me a break!
Please stop him, Narukami!
Huh? Why?
I can't go with you guys watching!
Excuse me?!
Well, shit! It's your fault if my bladder bursts!
You're unbelievable!
It's not like I wanted to watch anyway!
What is it? What's wrong?!
What is that?
R-Right back at you.
I-It can talk?!
I'm a bear.
I've lived here for a bear-y long time!
Wh-What's with this guy?
This is beyond ridiculous!
Keep your voices down.
You should go back to bear you came from.
U-Use this and get outta here!
The Shadows... The Shadows will...
Shadows?
Oh, my! Oh, my!
Why'd you put them on?
Something's there!
They're here!
What's his problem?
Wh-What are those things?!
Satonaka!
I'm done for...
I can't...
I can't move my legs.
I am thou.
Thou art I.
They stopped?
Wh-What's that?
Thou hath opened thine eyes.
The time is now!
Pe...
Per...
Perso...
Persona!
Narukami?
Damn you!
Izanagi!
A-Awesome...
Persona...
So this is my power.
The Midnight Channel airs on rainy nights.
I'll let it slide.
That's why you came!
You were just looking for fun!
Stop it!