Only cruel words flood the town at random
Never more will that sad voice flow by
Casual days bid their goodbyes
We have lost our
irreplaceable days together
The misty rain hides the sun
and steals our light
I was worried,
having lost everything I believed in
But I will never forget
the days I spent with everyone
Never more will I be
alone in the darkness
I will find everything dear to me
that I've lost
Never more, for I am sure that
your voice will lead the way
But I will never forget
the days I spent with everyone
Never more will I be
alone in the darkness
I will find everything dear to me
that I've lost
Never more, for I am sure that
your voice will lead the way
I still remember
The nights I spent with you
Those wonderful memories...