Welcome to the Velvet Room.
Let's see what fate has in store for you.
Oh my!
Dear guest,
a peril unlike any other is imminent.
You will face a terrible ordeal.
One so horrible that the combined strength of all of your Arcana
may not be enough to stop it.
I shall pray for your safe return.
Maru-Q!
This spring, one girl levels up to become a high school idol!
I'm Risette!
This time,
I'm gonna take on a surprising challenge!
Stripping!
Strip?!
Oh, I'm so embarrassed!
But, if a thing's worth doing,
it's worth doing all the way!
I'm gonna bare it all for you!
Stay tuned!
Hell—
She said "strip," right? Right?!
She did.
Is it me, or are these shows getting crazier and crazier?!
Calm down.
Huh? Okay...
Her Shadow self is probably just doing whatever it wants again.
Think Rise's in the TV now?
I'm sure of it.
We couldn't prevent it this time either,
even when we knew who the target would be.
Let's go tomorrow.
Okay, sure.
Figures.
Huh?
Teddie?
What's wrong?
Everyone was having fun out there, and you all forgot about me.
I was abandoned.
Were you lonely?
I was bored and got all listless.
That crap aside—
What are you calling "crap"?!
I'm a useless bear. I don't even know what I am.
Stop rollin' around!
I couldn't figure it out, and no one would come visit me.
Teddie, we need to—
I was so lonely that I tried to cry, but I couldn't!
When I'm alone, I think too much. It makes me even lonelier.
We'd never forget about you.
We think of you too, sometimes.
Can I try scoring with you two someday?
Sure, go right ahead!
Can we please drop the whole "scoring" thing?
Teddie, is Kujikawa Rise in here?
Kujikawa Rise?
Rise's really here?
The nose knows!
Dude, isn't this one of those clubs you always find in resort towns?!
Our inn is not like that!
God dammit! I can't see anything!
Kanji, you still don't have any glasses!
Oh boy, I totally forgot.
Here.
Why do these seem different?
Y-You look great!
Yo, Ted! Why the hell did I get stuck with these?!
Oh dear! You don't like them?
Fuck no!
I'm kind of excited.
So this is what it's like inside.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Welcome!
Let me guide you through this dazzling world.
There are so many Risettes.
Wow! I've seen them all!
She wore that in her third photo album!
It's showtime for Risette's dynamite body!
Oh, and that cheerleader's from her second album!
Thanks for the wait.
Risette!
Shut up!
Today, you're gonna see every last inch of me!
What's that? You don't believe me?
Okay, okay!
Just follow me, and I'll prove I'm every bit as good as my word!
This is the real me.
Were we like that?
That's goin' kinda far.
Those are that Rise girl's true feelings.
No one sees the real me.
Hmph.
Talk about a stiff crowd.
Maybe I should bring in our special guest!
What guest?
Today's guest is...
Kujikawa Rise!
Stop it. Please stop it.
Rise!
They're here!
Oh geez!
Dear guests, please mind your manners and refrain from touching the dancers.
Glasses, my glasses!
My glasses, my glasses...
Persona!
Let's finish this quick!
It repelled our attacks!
Then let's try physical attacks.
Geez, there's no end to them!
No, this isn't...
Aw! You wanna show your stuff, don'tcha?
Lookie! Look! C'mon!
See the real me! C'mon!
Stop it!
That isn't the real...
Don't give me that!
So who's the real you?
Well? Who's the real you?
The real me?
Dammit! Where are my glasses?
You looking for these?
Not too shabby!
They're going down.
Persona!
Dammit!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
Damn, he's good!
What a bulldozer.
Now tell me!
Who's the real Rise?
I'm the real Rise.
I don't know! Who is the real me?!
I am the real Rise.
You're me.
And obviously, I'm you.
No! No, you're not!
I'm sick of being some airhead cliché who takes it all with a smile!
Watch closely and see...
the real me.
No,
you're not...
Don't say it!
You're not me!
Here it comes!
This is it!
I am a Shadow...
The true self...
What's going on?
Rise!
Narukami, it's you...
Satonaka, Amagi, protect Rise!
You got it!
Okay!
I see you!
Whoa!
Teddie, watch over her.
Gotcha!
You're so transparent!
She dodged everything?
Don't tell me that light...
It's scanning our Personas' attacks.
Analysis complete!
Here comes my counterattack!
Fire!
M-Master! Guys!
Narukami...
That gotcha good!
Shit...
Here comes round two!
I... I gotta do something.
I gotta help.
But what can I do?
I can't do anything!
I'm so beary useless!
Take that!
Talk about lame!
I think it's about time
I got rid of you.
Shit!
Are we going to die?
Teddie, take Rise and run.
Abandon you? Only I'd get away?
Am I going to be all alone again?
Goodbye... forever.
Stop it.
That's enough!
Please stop this!
Annoying bitch!
You wanna go first?
Huh?
Teddie!
Why am I stepping forward?!
Wh-What the hell?!
What's with this high-energy reading?
I'm going bear-serk!
My body's moving on its own!
S-Stay back!
Don't do it!
Teddie!
It's... It's overloading!
Ugh...
You idiot! You coulda died!
Did I help?
You did more than help!
You saved our lives.
Yeah! You were really cool!
I guess you could score with me.
Teddie...
You protected me.
I know how much it hurts
to not know who you really are.
But you don't have to do it alone.
Let's figure it out together.
Teddie...
We have Master and the others, too.
I'm sorry I put you all through this.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah...
It's been a while since someone last said that to me.
I'm sorry.
I was trying to figure out who the real me was.
But I realize now that I was on the wrong track.
There is no "real" me. It just doesn't exist.
There's no real me?
You, me, and even Risette...
They were all born from me.
What's this?
It's your Persona.
My Persona?
Hey!
No fair!
She passed out.
I can't blame her.
We're barely hanging in there ourselves.
True enough.
Yeah...
Anyway, let's go.
I'm worried about Teddie—
There is no real me?
Real? Me?
Who's that talking?
What's going on?!
That's...
Is... Is that the other Teddie?
Why does this feel so strange?
Such foolishness!
The truth is unattainable. It will always be shrouded in fog.
I am a Shadow... The true self...
Though you reach through the murk...
and the gloom to grasp something, you have no means to know...
it is the truth.
What the hell?!
He's gonna pull us in!
In which case, why?
What sense is there in yearning for truth?
Oh no! Oh dear, oh dear, oh dear!
Teddie!
How do you find something when you know not what you search for?
You undergo suffering because of your search for the truth.
What do you mean?!
Well, I will grant you one truth.
You will all die here.
You're...
Hold Himiko down so she doesn't get pulled in.
Himiko?
She's my Persona.
Izanagi!
Persona!
Himiko!
There's something in there besides Teddie.
What is it?
I don't know.
The fog's keeping me from analyzing it.
Wh-Where am I?
It's here too!
You will vanish into nothingness here.
Wh-What the heck?! No!
You are hollow. Empty.
Empty?!
You have no lost memories.
You are but a mere—
I'm not listening! I'll find the answer for myself.
There is no answer.
I'll look anyway!
I may be hollow, but I'm not a useless bear!
I don't wanna disappear.
I don't wanna leave Master and my friends!
You would put yourself through more anguish in your quest for answers?
Your choice is incomprehensible.
Found it!
It's just below his chest.
I can't hang on!
Izanagi!
It stopped.
Teddie!
Grizzly...
Teddie, you alive?
Oh, my, my.
Wh-What the heck?!
What happened to my beautiful fur?
At least he seems okay.
Even Teddie had a hidden side to him, huh?
Huh?
I don't know who I am.
I've thought that maybe there is no answer.
But I'm here!
I live here!
I'm right there with you.
Rise!
Let's search for our answers together.
Teddie, you aren't alone.
Master!
Dude, we'll help you figure it out.
Y-You guys...
I'm one lucky bear!
A Persona?
I have my own Persona?
I can sense strong power from it.
It's awesome, Teddie.
Thanks a lot, Rise.
Thanks. This is close enough.
Get some rest.
But Teddie isn't resting at all.
While I wait for my fur to grow back, I'm gonna train real hard!
Just wait until I make my comeback!
And once again, you'll be begging for my help!
I'm glad I came to this town.
Huh?
There's something I can do here.
I have a place where I belong.
How so?
I'm gonna help search for the killer.
I see.
Let's give it our all, Yu!
May I make this my special place?
Uh, sure...
Aren't you the one treating it like a game?
That's the prince of Junes for you.
I'll finally get to enjoy my sweet teen years!
They caught the suspect?
This is awesome!
I'm amazing!