Glaciers of ideas, importing
To my friends, then exporting
To the next, keeping it open
We want no closing
Even without doughs our thoughts can be dope and
This mind trade no one can stop
An act of thinking is terrible to stop
We just wanna change up, not drop
And my crew can rock it like uprock
Life is tedious if it ain't flowing
Copy and paste? Constant defaulting?
Put my courage to it
Begin showing off
That's the way we wanna live
Keep going, yeah!
What was so much of transparency
Turned into bright expectation
My instinct tells me to keep going together, going together
It's breathtaking moments in life
Addicted to it, minds craving more and more
I'm believing you and I can do anything
We can change the world
Hey, sky's the limit, we can spread wings
to roadless travel, together we go