I'm sorry it had to come to this.
Farewell.
Yep, perfect!
Are you serious?! That sounds like some cheesy movie title!
Then how about,
"The Legend of Narukami Yu: The Sacred Dragon Sword of Wrath"?
What's he even fighting?
It's not a kung-fu movie, you know!
And you're in the way!
You're mean!
Shut up! I'm the sponsor here!
Good to see you're in such high spirits.
Oh, thanks for having us over.
Take your time with it.
Chie,
can you try this for me?
Lemme see.
Hm, it feels a bit too weak.
It doesn't have that special kick to it.
Then how about I add this?
Sh-Should I help?
You can't! This is your going away party, after all!
Just take it easy and chat with me!
And why are you taking it easy?
Wow, you've got a knack for this stuff, Tatsumi!
They're all so cute!
It's... uh...
Thanks.
Master!
How about putting this outside on the door?
Oh, hell no!
Narukami, wanna taste it?
Here, have a taste of Heaven!
Stop it!
Why would you poison him at his going away party?
Then you eat it!
Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
Shit, dude. A farewell party?
I never thought you'd actually leave.
I can't imagine my days without you!
I'm home!
Welcome back, Nanako.
Big Bro, you've got mail.
Thanks.
Oh, I forgot to buy octopus for Dad.
I gotta go back to get some!
Then how about we go together?
Hey, you'll come back when you have time, right?
Yeah, I think I'll come back during summer vacation.
Oh, and the May holidays too.
Hurray! Then it's all right!
Yeah.
Nanako?
I wanna stay with you...
Promise you'll never forget me!
I won't.
I promise.
It's a promise!
Narukami, wanna taste it?
Here, have a taste of Heaven!
You've got a knack for this stuff, Tatsumi!
They're all so cute!
Narukami?
What's wrong?
I bet that disgusting thing is what's wrong!
Then you eat it!
I'm home!
Big Bro, you've got mail.
I'm sure you're surprised to get this letter out of the blue.
I'm writing this because there's something I need to tell you.
It's true that my game is over.
As you all insisted at the time, I'll abide by the rules of this world.
But there's still this feeling I can't shake.
It's about how it all started.
About that Midnight Channel...
Now I remember... Before I heard the rumors at the station...
Someone else told me about it when I first came to town...
And I was intrigued when I noticed that something similar was written on Namatame's report as well.
But I can't remember who it was that told me.
Since Namatame and I both gained our power after coming to Inaba...
I thought that had something to do with it.
That's all.
I don't know if any of this will be useful or not, but I hope it can help somehow.
The source of the Midnight Channel rumor
and their powers...
You could use Personas from the very start and enter TVs too, right?
Yeah.
That means you're a person who had power from the beginning, like Namatame and Adachi.
There's something beyond what we can see.
The Midnight Channel and the ability to enter TVs...
If they were really separate, they
wouldn't fit together like this, right?
So you think the person Adachi mentioned,
the one who told him about the Midnight Channel,
also has something to do with the power to enter TVs?
Did I strike gold again?
I see... If they're somehow related...
So, do you have any idea?
If we knew when you got your power to enter TVs,
we might be able to find the person who started the rumor of the Midnight Channel.
The reason I got this power...
Well, I remember having this dream...
the night I came to town.
Could that dream be the reason then?
You had a dream without any discernible catalyst, then?
Well...
Is there something else?
The day I arrived,
I remember going straight to my uncle's...
No, wait! I remember now!
Here, have a taste of Heaven!
Why?
I'm back!
Big Bro...
Nanako,
remember the day I came to town?
We went somewhere before coming home, right?
Do you remember?
Um... Yeah.
What's gotten into you?
Tell me!
The gas station.
When I got back from the bathroom,
you were talking to the weird attendant.
You looked sick after that...
Where are you going?
What's wrong?
If you're feeling sick, you should go home.
Who...
Who are you?
Well, that's a weird question to ask.
Who are you?!
I didn't think you'd make it all the way to me.
Indeed, I never expected this at all.
You're really something.
You gave the power to Adachi, Namatame, and me?
What, you don't remember?
Very well.
Do you remember now?
It was the handshake greeting.
A handful of strangers were more than sufficient to stimulate a small place like this.
But it seems the stimulus was stronger than I imagined.
It was enough to envelop this town with fog...
and later lift it.
Who are you?!
I am Izanami.
Ameno-Sagiri, ruler of the fog, is merely an aspect of myself that I birthed long ago.
You created the Midnight Channel and spread the rumors of its existence?
Close.
Yes, it was I who created what you refer to as the Midnight Channel.
But that's not the whole truth.
What do you mean?
I've only been observing.
Has it not given you everything you've wanted?
It was always your individual wills that would determine what appeared on it.
Humans ache to expose their suppressed sides,
while the prying eyes around them are curious to see them laid bare.
The want to show and the want to see...
I granted a "window" that catered to both.
And that's the Midnight Channel?
Do you understand now?
I merely gave you what you wanted.
But I guess this comes with the foolish nature of being mortal.
The Midnight Channel only showed you what you wanted to see.
It showed you your desires in their purest form.
Don't you see how foolish you've been?
You don't want the truth.
You see only what you want to see and believe only what you want to believe.
Your desire is for a world enshrouded in fog.
Do you understand?
In eternal, never-lifting fog,
you will always see the world you want to see.
That is true happiness for you humans.
Like hell it is!
How could a world covered in fog bring happiness?
Can you honestly say that?
What do you mean?
Do you want to see the truth?
Do you really want to remember the cruel reality?
Cruel...
reality?
I see...
I...
No!
This is the cruel reality.
Is that all you've got?
You'll have to do better than that.
Master!
The will of all humans...
You disturb what they want to see.
They desire to live in the fog.
Yosuke!
You okay, Yu?
Sorry, partner...
Yosuke!
This is it for me...
What's this?
Let go!
Chie!
Stop! Stop!
Let go! Let go!
No! No!
Chie! Help! Narukami!
No! Stop! Please stop this!
Don't you understand?
You only suffer because of your search for the truth.
Therefore,
you should just live in a world covered by fog.
That is true happiness for you.
Yep, perfect!
Are you serious?! That sounds like some cheesy movie title!
Those're so cute!
It's not a kung-fu movie, you know!
Guys...
We'll be together forever, right?
What are you talking about?
Of course we will!
But I'm the only one who gets to be together-together with you.
There she goes again...
Here, have a taste of Heaven!
Stop it!
Why would you poison him—
Master!
How about putting this outside on the door?
Sounds good.
Dude, are you serious?
Try putting these in too.
Isn't that going a bit too far?
It's fine.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry it had to come to this.
Farewell.
Big Bro...
Big Bro, you'll be okay, right?
I believe that you'll come back!
Nanako...
You helped me.
Don't you lose, Narukami!
I'm counting on you, you know!
I could break out of my slump thanks to you!
He can read my moves?
Thank you, Master!
You taught me something important.
You'll be all right.
Even if we're apart...
I believe in you!
You helped me a lot.
I was supposed to be there for you, but it ended up the other way around.
But because of that, we became...
a real family.
What?
I was afraid of a tomorrow without everyone.
I was afraid I'd lose my friends and have to go on alone.
I don't want to be alone anymore.
I've had my share of solitude!
Yeah.
That's right!
This is the end!
I wanted to stay with everyone.
I didn't care if it was just a illusion in the fog.
I don't want to live a life without being connected to anyone!
I don't care as long as I'm with everyone!
Yeah, I don't need the truth.
As long they're with me, I don't care if it's an illusion.
You're me.
I'm not alone anymore!
Even if you lose everything,
your soul shall never be alone.
Never forget that.
This is a crystal of power which you have nurtured through your journey.
An orb that repels fabrications of all sorts, dispels lies, and shines upon the truth.
Thank you.
How have you returned?
So that's your true form?
It matters not.
The will of all mankind will pull you under again.
What?
Impossible!
Can the will of so few surpass the will of all mankind?!
Why? Why don't you understand?
It's impossible for humans to grasp the truth with their own hands.
You're not the one who gets to make that decision.
Your friends are no longer with you.
Will you go on living alone?
I...
am not alone!
Instead of endless struggle, wouldn't it be easier to wrap oneself in lies and live in blissful ignorance?
Allow me to show you...
human potential!
Do you think yourself a god?
What?
If only they'd open their eyes and look ahead, they could see...
...the truth!
I'll dispel the fog that covers our path!
I believe in the Myriad Truths ahead of us!
Myriad Truths?
I see.
You have lifted the fog in this world, as well as the fog in your own.
And whether that will lead to happiness or not rests upon your shoulders.
Yeah, leave it to us.
Children of man...
Well done!
Where am I?
Am I still inside the TV world?
Could this be what the TV world is supposed to look like?
How marvelous! A turning point in your destiny, wouldn't you say?
This journey was a fruitful one.
Now that the fog of lies has lifted,
there is nothing to prevent you from moving forth.
You are free to walk your own path.
This will be the last time we summon you here.
Huh? I thought...
Where are we?
It's so pretty!
Guys...
This...
I've wanted to see this sight again for so long!
Everywhere in this world used to look like this a long time ago!
Hey, watch where you're rolling!
You're here!
Narukami!
Yu!
Dude!
Our contract has been fulfilled.
My own duties end here as well.
You were a truly remarkable guest.
Now go forth and see with your own eyes.
See the world you have won...
And the bright, magnificent future...
Well,
see ya.
Good luck over there too.
If anything happens on your end, we'll come running!
Until we meet again, okay?
I'll be waiting for you!
Goodbye and take care.
I'll be looking forward to seeing you again!
Well, be careful.
I'll see you, Big Bro!
Buh-bye!
Yeah.
You take care too!
Thank you for everything!
Stay well until we meet again someday!
You'll always be my "Master"!
Please don't forget about us over there!
Yu!
I love you!
I'll do my best! You'd better not run away too!
I'll always remember our time together!
Distance doesn't matter to us! Even if we're separated, we're still friends!
I'll never, ever...
forget you guys.
He's really gone.
It's sad he won't be around, but we'll be okay, right?
Doesn't matter how far apart we are.
The bonds we made will remain strong.
Everyone's heart is connected to the people they know and trust.
It's those bonds that let us all search for our purpose in life.
As long as it's a purpose you believe in,
there'll always be someone who can help you fulfill it.
For you, me, and everyone else...
There are no barriers. Our hearts are one.