Welcome to the Velvet Room.
Dear guest,
I see a lack of caution in your demeanor.
The fog threatens to grow thicker once more.
Your journey is far from over.
No...
In fact,
I fear the worst has yet to come.
But you still have quite some time left.
You should proceed at your own pace.
This is becoming most fascinating.
It's News EYE!
Tonight's report...
features the high school student and private detective
who assisted the police with investigating the string of serial murders in Inaba.
His handsome looks are sweeping the nation.
It's the Detective Prince,
Shirogane Naoto!
The pleasure is all mine.
So then,
are the mysteries surrounding the case finally cleared up?
Not exactly.
When I cast my eye over the case as a whole,
I detect a few things that seem out of place.
Oh? Like what?
Unfortunately, I cannot divulge details at this time,
but I will say that something feels off.
Uh, well, um... Shirogane?
Huh?
I met him at the festival.
But this matter claimed the lives of three people.
Hence, I believe even the smallest inconsistency must be investigated.
I was kinda surprised.
By what?
Naoto!
The distinguished Detective Prince?
Oh, are you talking about the report last night?
Yeah.
I didn't think he was the type to go after the spotlight like that.
Indeed,
I prefer not to go on TV.
Naoto!
Do you have a moment?
Thanks! Come again!
Now then,
could you please indulge my current theory on the case?
Hey, now!
The case is already closed.
Didn't you say something felt wrong?
Yes.
First, regarding commonalities between the victims...
All of them were kidnapped before they were murdered.
The victims were all locals who had been the focus of recent media attention,
becoming suddenly well-known.
I don't believe there's anything intrinsically unique about the victims themselves.
Will you admit that a number of you...
fit these identical circumstances?
How do you figure that?
There was a long interval between the second and third deaths in this case.
But I discovered several similar disappearances had taken place that fit the aforementioned criteria.
Amagi Yukiko,
Tatsumi Kanji,
Kujikawa Rise.
All of you disappeared shortly after being shown on TV.
Either you escaped death somehow,
or you faked your own disappearances to divert attention from yourselves.
What are you getting at?!
Since some of you had ties to the victims,
perhaps one of you are...
Whoa, hold it! What—
Yosuke!
Hey, look! Isn't that the Detective Prince?
Let's take this elsewhere.
So you think that one of us is the killer?
I considered that possibility,
but now I believe exactly the opposite.
How so?
You aren't the culprits.
You may be the only ones with the means to pursue the true perpetrator.
Seen as a joining of forces between the rescued,
everything falls into place.
But there is a flaw in the theory.
It doesn't account for Mr. Morooka's murder.
He has never been broadcast on television nor gone missing.
We must also consider the condition of his corpse.
What do you mean?
He was hung upside-down just like Ms. Yamano and Konishi!
It's true he was found in a similar position.
The first two victims are still listed with an unknown cause of death,
but Mr. Morooka died of an easily identifiable blunt force trauma to the occipital cranium.
The police have not satisfactorily resolved this discrepancy,
yet they are desperate to close the case.
So?
Further action will be necessary to obtain...
decisive evidence.
How will this pan out?
H-Hey, where are you going?
You said something interesting to me not long ago.
"We go into the TV to rescue people after they get kidnapped."
Oh, well...
This is not a game for me either.
Wasn't that Naoto on the Midnight Channel last night?
It definitely looked like him.
I asked Teddie, and he said no one's on the other side.
But didn't we already catch the killer?
If the case is closed,
why did he show up on the Midnight Channel?
What exactly is the Midnight Channel, anyway?
Good evening, everyone.
I am the Detective Prince, Shirogane Naoto.
Welcome to "Experiment of the Century: The Genome Project."
I will be both experimenter and experimentee in a bodily alteration process!
A what?
I will use a forbidden yet wonderful process!
You shall witness my departure into a new realm!
The moment of a new birth!
From the chosen day forth, I shall walk a completely different path in life!
And I will share this glorious occasion with all of you!
Do stay tuned.
Hel—
Dude!
I-I just saw N-Naoto crystal clear!
Calm—
The hell's going on?!
I thought we caught the damn killer!
This proves that Naoto's gut feeling was right.
What good was it when he got himself kidnapped?!
Damn, he pisses me off!
Want me to gather the group?
Please.
Got it!
There's definitely someone in here.
And...
this world is growing larger.
Way to go, Rise!
My nose is worn out.
Want me to rub your shoulders?
Don't distract her!
What's going on?
Does this mean the case isn't over?
So it's still happening like before.
Nothing's changed.
I see!
That's why Naoto suddenly decided to go on TV.
I bet you're right.
Only locals who've been on TV have been kidnapped.
He made himself bait?
No way!
He could get killed!
That idiot!
The least he coulda done was warn us!
He said this wasn't a game to him.
What should I do?
It's my fault.
Because of what I said...
Rise...
It's no use.
I can tell he's here, but I can't find him.
It's too dangerous to wander around blindly.
We'd lose our bear-ings!
Damn it!
There's nothing we can do.
Let's leave for now.
So, if the case isn't over,
what's the deal with Kubo?
Didn't he kill King Moron?
Remember what Naoto said?
It's weird how they could only identify Mr. Morooka's cause of death.
Right.
And he's the only one who never entered the TV.
The killer didn't change his methods with King Moron.
It was a different killer to begin with.
So the person who kidnapped Naoto is the real culprit?
But Kubo confessed that he killed the others, remember?
So he took the rap for someone else?
Isn't that weird?
And there's something else bugging me.
It's, uh...
Who cares about someone behind bars?
If we don't hurry, that idiot's gonna die!
Sorry, but I need more information so I can get a better picture of him.
More info, huh?
Dammit!
We don't know shit about him!
Let's split up and gather information on Naoto.
Hey...
I don't know if this is related to Naoto or not,
but hasn't the town seemed weird as of late?
How so?
Everyone seems strangely happy.
They're always talking about others.
That's nothing new, you know.
Isn't it their way of showing they're relieved that the case is closed?
But still,
it doesn't feel right.
It's like they're afraid of something.
The Detective Prince?
Oh, doesn't he have like seven secretaries?
It's so cool how he gets a different one every day!
Isn't it?
Care to pick me up and make me your secretary...
every day of the week?
Shuddup!
Thanks...
He was awful!
Talk about gross.
Okay, got it.
Satonaka hasn't had any luck yet either.
Shit!
This town's friggin' puny,
so why can't we find any useful info?!
He stands out like a sore thumb!
Hello.
I'm busy right—
What?!
What is it?
My old lady...
got taken to the hospital!
What?!
You brought someone here, not the other way around?!
Shh!
Don't shout in a hospital.
B-But...
I saw the poor boy get hit by a bicycle right in front of me.
Since he hit his head, I wanted him to see a doctor.
But they said he's fine. Isn't that wonderful?
Cut the crap!
You're shouting again.
Dammit!
I'm fine!
I won't go down without a fight.
It's not like you to worry.
Shut up, you old hag!
Oh, yes.
Those stuffed animals you made to boost store profits are quite popular.
Thank you.
They're knitted animals,
not stuffed animals.
I swear, everyone's driving me nuts.
Sorry about that.
I'm glad it wasn't anything serious.
Let's make up for lost time after we eat.
Dammit!
Pulling shit like that, never considering how others might feel!
Do you mean your mom or Naoto?
Huh? Well, both.
Here's your beef bowl.
Thanks.
Oh, right.
Since you go around town making deliveries, have you heard anything about Naoto?
The Detective Prince...
got in a fight.
A fight?!
With who?
He was arguing with an officer?
Why?
Supposedly, he frequently criticized how they were handling the case.
At any rate,
Naoto's obsession with the case seemed abnormal.
I wonder why he was so fixated on it.
The way the police treated him like a kid might've had something to do with it.
Aika knew all that?
No, she only told us that he was fighting with an officer.
You know? That lame cop.
Oh, Adachi!
I see... So he's super stubborn.
And he's surprisingly emotional.
I'm getting a picture of him.
What is this place?
Doesn't it remind you of those secret hideouts in live-action shows?
I've heard those are really tough shoots.
It's all dusty and hot as Hell with the bright lights.
What's wrong?
Teddie,
aren't the buildings and events in this world made from people's repressed emotions?
Yes!
Do you remember what Naoto said on the Midnight Channel?
From the chosen day forth, I shall walk a completely different path in life!
I thought Naoto was rejecting his life as a boy detective.
What of it?
This secret lab...
It looks like one of those old sets where boy detectives or heroes solve cases.
You have a point.
But if this came from Naoto's mind,
he isn't as grown up as he looks.
I don't know about any of that,
but I do know one thing.
What's that?
He's...
running away from something too.
Warning! Intruders!
Hey! Looks like you're right.
Naoto!
Ah.
It's about time you arrived.
Dealing with this child has been quite a pain.
No! No, no, don't go!
That's Naoto's Shadow?
It looks like a little kid!
You guys, heads up!
They're bear-low us too!
Here they come!
It's useless speaking with you.
I'm leaving.
Why?
Why are you leaving me here?!
Why am I always left all alone?!
It's so lonely.
I don't wanna be alone!
You wear the same face as me.
It's as if you're implying we're one and the same.
But...
the difference between you and me is...
Why delude yourself?
You know the truth, don't you?
I am you!
Persona!
These childish gestures are no mere affectation.
They're the truth.
Naoto, don't argue with him!
No!
He has to face this.
Haven't we...
...all had to go through this?
The fools all say it, don't they?
"You're only a child! Just a measly kid!"
As long as they need it, you're an ace detective.
But once you're done,
it's back to the playpen with you.
You haven't the means to deal with society's two-faced nature.
You're just a lonely child.
I wanna be a big boy right now.
Then they'll see who I am.
I want a reason for me to stay.
That's enough.
I can find my own reason for living.
You are but a child.
How can you change that essential truth?
Stop it!
At your core,
you admire the sort of "strong" and "cool" men who populate detective fiction.
But in trying to emulate them,
you must know that, in truth, you're nothing of the sort.
You're lying!
Shirogane Naoto...
Isn't it a cool, masculine name?
But...
Don't!
But a name doesn't change the truth.
Stop it!
It doesn't let you cross...
the barrier between sexes.
How could you become an ideal man...
when you were never male to begin with?
What?!
Did he...
Did I hear that right?
H-He's not a guy?!
I won't throw a tantrum.
That accomplishes nothing!
How often I've heard those words from the adults!
"Throwing a tantrum won't solve anything, Naoto."
They made you cry, didn't they?
Yet here you are, mimicking those same men.
What exactly are you trying to justify?
You needn't suffer anymore.
I know exactly how you feel.
After all, I am you.
No!
Don't say it!
No, let her get it out.
Kanji!
Otherwise...
she'll continue to suffer!
You...
You're not me!
We...
I am a Shadow... The true self...
We just gotta do our thing...
...and kick the Shadow's ass!
How dare you act so almighty?
I hate violent guys who let their emotions get the best of them!
Come then!
It's body-altering time!
No!
Stop it!
Let's do it!
Yeah!
What?
Are you sick of yourselves too?
Then...
Let's begin the special operation!
Yosuke!
Did she modify my body?
No, this isn't a modification.
She didn't modify you in that sense.
She made you older!
She what?!
You serious?!
Oh, Yo-Yo-Yosuke!
Th-Those wrinkles!
His teeth!
Liver spots!
Now...
for the operation!
No!
Let me alter your bodies already!
Narukami!
You've been so good to me.
She's one crazy lady.
Don't forget about me!
No one needs me anymore.
Everyone, run for it!
I feel so full of life!