I can handle things on my own
Even holding down the fort
So Dad, it's okay if you're out late
When I get lonesome on my own
I open the window
I want you to watch me
from above the heavens, Mom
I still remember your warm smiles
Every single one from the day I lost you
The two of us have fun
Cooking and eating together
Big Bro's here
So I'm not lonely
But really, I want
The whole family to be together
I'm just holding these feelings back
I wanna see you, I wanna see you
I wanna see you right now
And when I do
Smile like you used to
Don't be angry as you hug me tenderly
Cover the hole in my heart
Overflowing with tears
With your warm hand
When you do, I can see
There's pain aside from my own
We can overcome our loneliness
Just as long as we're together
I'll say it whenever and wherever
As many times as you like
Dad, please don't forget
I love you