Welcome to the Velvet Room.
I see you've overcome your most difficult battle yet.
You've done well.
You probably need some time to rest and recuperate.
Time is of the essence, but knowing when to take a break is also important.
Did you catch a cold?
You poor thing.
Now you won't get cold.
Goodbye, Mr. Fox!
I heard you came home drenched yesterday.
What happened to your umbrella?
I lost it.
Hey now! We just bought it, too.
I'm sorry.
I'm back.
Welcome home!
Oh, you were out late.
I was busy.
I'm back.
Welcome home!
Should I warm your dinner up?
Sorry, but I already ate.
You did?
Oh, Nanako. Have you heard of Neo Featherman?
Yeah, everyone loves him.
I see. Heroes these days are something else, aren't they?
At Junes, every day is Customer Appreciation Day!
I'm back.
Come see for yourself, and get in touch with our products!
Hey, you! I hear you've been coming home late!
Oh yeah, I guess.
There's wasabi in it.
Did you forget to wipe it off?
Here. I'll do it for you.
What'll it be?
Halibut!
You have great taste, Nanako!
Hm... I'll have urchin roe.
You bastard! That was the only one!
You know how it is! You snooze, you lose.
Anyway, back to Yu!
You've been acting strange lately.
So you got a girl?
You did, didn't you? You got a girl!
It's not a girl.
Hey, Dojima!
We may have solved the case, but watch the booze!
Hey, Yu!
Y-Yes?
If it isn't a girl, what's keeping you out so late?
Actually...
Since when were you such a tease?
Yu, that was a riot!
What's wrong?
Just leave me alone.
Still, that killer was something else.
I can't believe he was just a high schooler.
But I'm glad we caught him.
His fingerprints were on the victims' clothes, so this case is as good as closed!
If you doubt the one you love, solve the case promptly with the power of magic!
Leave the investigating to us!
I'm the Magical Detective Loveline!
When our eyes lock, a new case starts up.
I'll trail after—
I'm off.
Take care!
All right!
Leave the investigating to me!
I'm the Magical Detective Loveline!
Want me to fill you with holes?!
He's the culprit!
We're on the case!
Huh? Nana, what are you doing?
Oh, Mas—
Stop that!
Huh? Why?
I'm trailing him.
Trailing him, huh?
Hm... My nose says to go this way!
But Big Bro's over there.
C'mon! Just trust me!
I'm gonna need a new stomach for these!
Teddie, where's Big Bro?
They're all round.
Want me to fill you with holes?!
Roly-poly, roly-poly...
Roly-poly, roly-poly, roly!
It's Loveline!
Roly-poly, roly-poly, roly-poly!
We lost him.
Let's try again tomorrow!
This is our little secret!
I'm the Magical Detective Loveline!
Want me to fill you with holes?!
I'll get to the bottom of this today!
Huh?
Where'd he go?
Nanako?
What's with the costume?
I can't believe Yu would make poor Nanako worry!
But you gotta admit, he hasn't been hanging out with us lately.
Nope. He's not picking up.
Then let's go look for him.
Right on! There's no point thinking about it.
Nanako, we'll help out, so let's get to it!
Yeah, thank you!
Phew, I'm beat.
Are you okay, Nanako?
Yeah, I'm fine.
This is pretty tough without any clues to go on.
I didn't think he'd wander very far.
Teddie took the bus?!
Huh? Is that bear your friend?
Hey, Teddie! What are you doing out here?
Huh? Why aren't you saying anything?
What a weird bear.
I-I'm not a suspicious bear.
Doesn't his voice sound off?
And he's all stiff.
Yeah, it doesn't seem natural.
He's normally more, uh, hyperactive.
Like how he randomly rolls around.
Oops!
That was so forced.
Wh-Why'd he run from us?
He's the culprit!
Huh?
Yeah, I understand.
Big Bro said he'd be home late.
What's he up to?
He's acting weird.
What's gotten into him?
Keep at it, Loveline!
Yeah! I'll continue conducting the investigation!
You know some big words...
I have to solve the mystery today!
You're surprisingly forward.
I don't have a problem with that.
What?
Huh? Where are we going?
Don't you worry about that.
Big Bro was walking with some woman.
Who could she be?
Huh? Nanako?
Nana!
Something bothering you?
It's Big Bro!
You see, Yuuta isn't really my son.
Whoa, she's right!
This is serious!
Was this your "urgent business"?
Dude! It's even an older woman!
I was in the middle of practice.
Oh-ho! So that's Master's type.
Huh? That's not the same woman I saw earlier.
For real?!
Huh? What the?!
She has a kid?!
No way! You're lying!
I won't believe it till I see it!
I'll go double check!
Good idea! Let's go together.
Huh? But we don't really care.
It'd be embarrassing if he caught us.
At ease, ladies!
I came prepared for something like this.
Hey, is this even a disguise?
This is a job for the pros.
What now?
Isn't that great, Chie?
Hey, save it for later.
She's super old!
He looks lonely.
Big Br—
What is it?
Uh, nothing.
It's nothing.
Okay. Then I'll see you later.
Take care.
Ouch!
Adachi screwed things up again,
so I'm stuck here for a while longer.
Sorry. I even promised I'd take you to the festival.
Loveline!
What's wrong?
The case will never be closed if the detective gives up.
Huh?
So don't drop the case...
until it's over.
I can't give up?
I'll leave the investigating to you!
'Kay!
If you doubt the one you love, solve the case promptly with the power of magic!
Leave the investigating to me!
I'm the Magical Detective Loveline!
We're on the case!
Where's Big Bro?
Damn! How'd they sell out?
I'm sorry.
Some gorgeous foreign boy who spoke all funny-like gobbled it up like you wouldn't believe!
He must've been a monster to have eaten all your shaved ice!
Just leave this to Loveline!
Huh?
I'd like to order a delivery.
Could you deliver some ice?
Thanks for the order.
Will she actually come?
Yep! Big Bro said she's amazing.
Cool. Thanks a bunch!
Loveline always helps those in need.
I'd like to order some shaved ice.
I'm sorry, but it's all sold out.
My, isn't she cute?
Big Bro!
Hey, you!
Can I see that?
Raise me toward the sun!
You're a lifesaver. Thanks.
Loveline always helps those in need.
Well? Don't I look great?
Yeah, you look cool!
You're supposed to say "cute."
Big Bro!
What's wrong?
Would you like me to hit your back?
I thought I was gonna die!
Are you okay?
Yeah, thanks.
Mister, do you make fireworks?
Yeah! Fireworks are like art to me.
Amazing!
I just love sitting and watching everyone's expressions at the festival
right before we shoot off the fireworks.
Why's that?
When I set off the fireworks, everyone around starts to smile.
Bringing a smile to their faces is really amazing!
Making people smile is... amazing?
Oh! It's just about time.
Just wait till you see my huge fireworks!
Big Bro!
Nanako?
What's wrong?
Where have you been, Big Bro?
Nanako, what's with that outfit? Where's your dad?
Big Bro, fireworks!
Yeah, indeed.
They're pretty.
Yeah. They're really pretty.
Mister!
Bringing a smile to their faces is really amazing!
Yeah!
Big Bro, you're amazing!
Huh?
Everyone was smiling!
Everyone?
You're amazing! Truly amazing!
Well? Have fun?
Yep, it was a blast.
Wasn't it great?
Yep!
Oh yeah, there's a surprise for you coming in two days.
What surprise?
Watermelon! Where's the watermelon?!
Geez, Kanji! They invited us over, so at least show some manners.
Watermelon!
Where is it?!
My uncle's getting it now.
Watermelon!
We gotta smack it open first.
Huh? Are we seriously gonna do that?
But doesn't it sound like fun?
I wanna do it too!
The splattering fruit juice! Bursts of joy! One night of love...
That bittersweetness of those days is the essence of youth!
That's the essence of youth!
I'm home!
Whoa, that's a lot of shoes! How many people are here?
Welcome home!
Let's split the watermelon open!
You wanted to?
I'm really sorry. It never occurred to me you'd want to do that.
Nanako, let's do it properly sometime.
Definitely!
Next time, we'll do it right - at the beach!
Oh, sounds good! But I think it'll have to wait until next year.
Will you play with me again next year?
Of course we will!
You bet!
Isn't that great, Nanako?
Yeah!
Gotta love watermelons!
This is bliss!
Watermelons are great!
Come to think of it, Big Bro...
Yeah?
What were you doing all summer?
Want me to fill you with holes?!
Oh, well...
You want me to grant their wishes?
I'm going to put everyone out!
Why don't the two of us go somewhere?
Yu!
In the end, I'm glad I met you there.
Damn you, Neo Featherman!