Welcome to the Velvet Room.
The Social Links you've cultivated have unlocked new powers.
Temperance, the Tower, Death, the Devil, and the Hermit.
I'm amazed you've obtained so many at once!
Very impressive!
You've already made an impressive number of Social Links.
As you converse and develop a deeper understanding with others,
your bonds will strengthen and facilitate another change in your powers.
Summer vacation's really over.
I got lost on the way to school.
It was a pretty long break.
Yeah, but c'mon, getting lost?
I'm surprised you even realized you got lost.
How could I not?!
Good morning.
I've been waiting for you.
You're— Wait, uh...
It's the "Little Detective."
It's Shirogane.
Please don't call me by any other weird names you've thought up.
I felt that greetings were somewhat in order.
Greetings?
The police investigation may be over,
but there are still several points that leave me unconvinced.
Plus, I have some family issues,
so I'll be staying here for a while.
I'll be a freshman here starting today.
Let's try to get along, okay?
This rocks!
I've been dying to go on this school trip!
We'll hit up all the tourist spots!
Take pictures with the girls!
Or maybe have a romantic encounter in an unfamiliar town!
"Day 1: Cultural exchange."
"Day 2: View factories and such during our free time."
"Day 3: Go home."
What's up with the cultural exchange crap?
It's like a social studies trip!
They want rural and suburban students to interact, so we'll be visiting a private school.
Don't we get any free time?
Is our free time really  free time?!
This trip's itinerary was supposedly created by King Moron.
This sucks!
Is King Moron tormenting us from beyond the grave?
Freshmen and sophomores get to go together starting this year!
How lucky!
With the decline in students,
they decided to save money by holding the trip every other year.
Well, I doubt we'll get bored with you guys around.
What's Tatsumi Port Island like?
It's a large city on an artificial island facing the ocean.
Hey, could we invite Naoto whenever we go out?
Over there.
I'm a little worried about him.
Didn't he come here specifically to help out with that case?
He may be a detective, but he's just a normal kid once the case is over.
Come to think of it, he's a fellow transfer student, huh?
Yeah...
Well, uh, next, I will explain about our educational institution and the reasons for its establishment!
This school's way too big!
Uh, I'd like to start with a proverb— Er, I can't waste too much of your time.
It's like three Juneses combined.
Narukami, this is a school, not Junes!
As such, I shall hereby draw this assembly to an end.
How was that funny?
Welcome, everyone, to Gekkoukan High School!
It's an honor to meet you all today.
I'm the student council president, Fushimi Chihiro from Class 3-B.
It's love!
Damn! She's the most bewitching bespectacled beauty I've ever beheld!
Those glasses are pretty hip.
I'll be the one showing you around campus.
It would be my honor.
This is the first time our school has invited another student body for a true cultural exchange.
We'll do our best to ensure a worthwhile experience for each and every one of you.
Well then, your group is going to have a special lecture in this room.
So, uh, does everyone know about the gods who made our country?
The two gods who made our country were the god Izanagi and the goddess Izanami.
I don't care about this!
I just want him to finish up so we can go.
We have lectures all day.
The two got along really well until one day.
What?! You serious?
You were great in class today, kiddos!
We're heading over to our lodgings for the night!
After all that today, I'm hoping tonight's rooming is something else!
Wow!
Yes!
All righty, here we are. The Seaside Clamshell Inn!
We'll be staying here tonight.
It just opened not too long ago, and the price was right!
Well, don't just stand there!
Those in front, get a move on! Come on in!
Is this really a normal hotel?
It just screams sketchy.
Really?
We don't have these modern hotels in Inaba, so I can't tell.
Um... This area is called "Shirakawa Boulevard," and it's...
They probably refurbished a place that had gone under, and, uh...
Oh, it's a love—
Whoa! That's far enough!
It's okay.
It doesn't sound weird when Narukami says it.
Yeah, he's okay.
What gives? You always go easy on him.
Faster than I expected.
If they were to meet me... I wonder, what the look on Yosuke's face would be like?
Where's that voice coming from?
Who's that?!
Hiya!
Shoo-bee doo-bee!
Teddie?!
What are you doing here?!
I couldn't bear the loneliness!
I knew where you were going thanks to Yosuke's "Trip Guide."
Hey, when did you see that?!
How'd you get here, anyway?
I took the train like a normal bear.
I swore off Topsicles and saved up the money I got working at Junes.
I had to take an unbearably slow train here!
Teddie, you've been through a lot.
Oh, Master!
But why'd you come dressed like that? You look like a freak!
I almost got thrown in the trash a couple times.
But I kept hanging onto the promise Yukiko made to go on a date with me!
I sure did.
In that case, let's all go out during our free time tomorrow.
Is that okay?
What?!
That's a bear-rilliant idea!
Shoo-bee doo-bee!
For the record, I'm cool with sharing a room with you girls.
Not happening.
I'm beat!
Would you like something to drink?
Look here. Isn't this bed awesome?
It's a waterbed!
This is fun.
I gotta check this out.
It's really bouncy!
You're getting too hyped up.
Switch on!
I don't believe it!
Oh, wow!
We're spinning! I'm gonna get dizzy!
This is kinda unnerving, isn't it?
Well, yeah...
How long are you going to stand there?
So, why don't we test out the bed?
Dude! Don't invite me to bed!
Wha— Fuck you!
I keep telling you I don't swing that way, dammit!
But there's no way to know for sure!
Hey, don't you trust me?!
Shoo-bee! Shoo-bee doo-bee!
You're pissing me off!
I know you—
Hey, guys!
Stop fighting!
Relax! Relax!
That hurt.
What was that for, punk?!
Wow! Those are some suspicious-looking buttons!
Bam! Bam! Bam! Bam! Bam!
Huh?
Yahoo! This is great!
Isn't this soothing?
Damn, I can't sleep here!
Yahoo!
Hey, move it!
I've had it...
I'm gonna sleep here with you!
School trips are supposed to be more...
You're fucking sleeping outside!
But I already took my bath and don't have a change of clothes!
How about a pic for posterity?
Don't you dare!
Sweet! I'm on a date!
I'm shopping with Chie, Yuki, and Rise!
Teddie, how about we go in that building?
Okay!
Dates are great!
Teddie seems to be having fun.
Why are we following them?
Because we don't know where to go.
...program independently a copy of Defendant A's middle school graduation speech.
They're still at it.
We'll give you the full story later in our feature program.
It's about the killer we caught.
People think it's cool to diss
anyone who looks antisocial.
Huh? Where are Teddie and the girls?
It looks like we lost them!
This sucks. Let's split up and look for them.
Hey, cut it out!
Aren't you ashamed of yourself for ganging up on him?!
This bitch is giving us lip.
You're gonna get it!
Fine! You can hit my face, my gut, or wherever!
But you better leave this kid alone!
That's messed up.
This is boring. Let's go.
Yeah, she's annoying.
Thank goodness they're leaving you alone now.
Thank you so much!
Narukami?
Are you okay?
Have you calmed down a little?
Yeah, I'm sorry I made you worry.
I just couldn't turn a blind eye when I saw them trying to mug him.
I told myself I just had to protect him.
Pretty stupid, huh?
No, it was really brave.
That's the least I could do for him.
You know, I wanna find my self-worth in something beyond simply being there for Yukiko,
so I'm always pushing myself,
telling myself I gotta get stronger and try even harder.
Satonaka, you're already working hard.
You think?
I count on you.
Really?!
I'm glad!
But I don't want you to push yourself too hard.
Huh?
It makes me worry.
Th-Thanks...
I-I got a text!
It's from Yukiko.
She said, "Rise's taking everyone out to a club."
We should go, too.
Yeah!
Wow. So this is a club.
Oh shoot, I'm getting pumped up!
Huh?
Whoa!
It's him!
My, I never expected to run into you here.
Is it permitted for high school students such as yourselves to be here?
Look who's talking!
What brought you here, anyway?
This is a reputable club, so I was checking it out.
It's not as if I was otherwise preoccupied.
Then let's hang out together.
Together? You're inviting me?
Why don't you eat with us?
If you aren't busy, why not?
I've been really eager to talk to you.
I'm curious how someone my age is working as a detective.
Let's go!
How about it?
Very well, if you insist.
What's up? You look a little red.
That's not true!
I'll go get us the VIP room.
Wow, a VIP room!
I know some people. Just give me a sec.
That's good!
It's really good!
Yukiko, how many have you had?
Are you sure this is all right? Isn't it expensive?
No worries.
When I held a secret show here, the power went out in the middle of it, and the gig was canceled.
So this is on the house today.
Whoa! You serious?
Then I won't hold back!
Yay! We won't hold back either! Right, Kanji?
Kanji, drink up and start singing!
Shut up! Leave me alone!
Kanji, you're so mean!
Kanji... Kanji. Kanji?
I Kanjecture that something's up!
Kanjecture?
Kanjecture!
There are good and bad Kanjectures.
Yukiko's a bit looser than usual, too.
Great Kanjecture!
Hey! Don't tell me this is...
I told 'em to give us soft drinks! They're non-alcoholic!
Sheesh, I was wondering why it's so hot.
I told them! I really did!
Are these seriously alcoholic... drinks?
Of course not.
I'm sure they aren't.
Hit me.
Kings Game!
Kanji!
Prepare the sticks!
Why should I?
The King's orders are absolute!
Get your butt in gear!
Here you go.
W-When did he get those?
The King's orders are absolute.
Oh, Yu!
Is he drunk?
Ta-da! Everyone, take your pick!
So who's the King?
Teddie's is red! Teddie's the King!
Man, this can't end well.
As King, I order number three to give me a smooch...
without delay!
Kissy!
Dude! Not number three!
How about number two?
Forget it! No take-backs, Kingy!
Smooch! Yay, smooch! Yay!
A-A smooch?
Kanji, I knew you had your eyes set on me.
Okay, I'll give you my innocence!
Whoa, don't! I'll freakin' kill you!
Only the first round, and two contestants have dropped out already.
Is it that kind of game?
On to round two!
Who's the King?
I'm the King.
N-No crazy orders this time.
That's not how it goes! If the last King demanded a smooch,
then the next order's gotta be more extreme.
They should rest on his lap!
Make 'em sit on his lap!
Skip straight to hugging!
I know! Piggybacks are all the rage.
Are they serious?
Go on. Make up your mind.
Number two!
I got number two.
Sit on my lap!
I-It's me.
The King's order is...
...absolute!
Wow, not bad!
Me next!
Chie, you gotta hug him like this!
Get with it.
Hey, lowly commoners! That King's mine!
Move it!
Oh, Yu...
Yu, don't hog all of them!
B-But I'm the King.
Me next! I'm the King! Actually, the Queen!
You didn't even draw a chopstick!
Let's have someone talk about something really embarrassing
that they'd never wanna tell anyone!
You're up, Naoto!
Huh?
You don't have to if you don't want to, Naoto.
No, I don't mind.
But in exchange, you all have to tell me about something as well.
Sure! Bring it on!
I can't think of any embarrassing stories, so I'll explain my past.
The Shirogane family line has been helping the police as detectives for generations.
It's the fifth generation with me,
and I'm living with my grandfather.
Just like the Kindaichi Case Files!
My grandfather has deep connections with the police
and looks after me, despite my youth and inexperience.
That's it?! No punchline?
No. Sorry for the letdown.
Naoto, that's so embarrassing!
I'm sleepy.
Fill her up, on the rocks.
Are you seriously drunk, dude?
Now it's your turn.
I would like to hear your answer.
A straight answer, please. What is your true involvement with the murder case?
You know, you're so good at killing the mood that it's almost funny.
Well, we go rescuing people who've been kidnapped by jumping into the TV!
And then, we use our Personas to beat up Shadows...
Persona!
Hey, watch it!
Are you mocking me?
Issh true!
Persona! Persona!
Sheesh, somebody put these two drunks to bed already!
I see now that you had no intention of telling me the truth.
But really, this isn't alcohol.
Good one!
No, I confirmed it when I first entered.
No alcohol has been served here since a rash of drunk driving last year.
Huh? Does that mean we're drunk off the atmosphere?
Who cares?
Good night!
How are we supposed to get back with three of them out cold? Right, Yu?
Fill her up, straight.
Is this a group of imbeciles?
Dang! This is good!
I came here a lot when we were shooting dramas.
They've got the best ramen in town.
Do you remember what happened last night?
Oh, I think the two us fell asleep quick. I heard it got pretty wild, though.
Right, Yu?
I took things a little too seriously.
My head is killing me.
It's on the house.
Aika.
What are you doing working here?
An acquaintance runs the shop, so I'm training here.
Wow! You even train during trips.
Isn't this the Hagakure Bow?
I didn't know it was on the regular menu now!
Eat up before it gets cold.
I wonder if I can eat it all.
I'll be a pal and help out!
I was still eating that!
But you were all done.
Was not!
It's just about time for us to head back.
It's that late already?
Looking back, I had a pretty good time.
What should we get Nanako?
Let's pick it out together!
All righty, let's go!
Wait!
I'm so stuffed I can't move...
Help me!
Let's leave him.
The Queen's orders are absolute.
Farewell, Teddie. I'm leaving you here along with the memories of my youth.
Wait! Help me! I can't cover my ticket back!
Right. Regarding those materials...
I'll take them. Send them over ASAP.
Let's split up and gather information on Naoto.
Hey!
I don't think of this as a game.
You could get killed!
He's just a little brat!
It's time for the body-altering operation!