Welcome to the Velvet Room.
These are the bonds that may take root in your heart.
I'm amazed that you might obtain all these Arcana at once!
Oh! It makes my heart flutter!
I believe you may be just the person I'm looking for.
Narukami Yu is a student from Class 2-2 at Yasogami High School.
This is a record of his exciting summer.
I'm ho—
Didn't you take your Loveline umbrella with you?
I lost it.
August 7th.
It appeared before him without any warning.
I need a job.
What is it?
You want me to grant this wish?
But I don't even know where he is.
What is it?
Hello, I'm Mrs. Nakajima.
Uh, about your ad for a tutor...
Oh, that!
You're amazing!
Just so you know, I have no intention of going to Yasogami High School.
It's just that no one else could start tutoring right away.
What is it?
Nothing. I was just looking at you.
Are you even any good?
You betcha!
I'm home.
Welcome home!
Oh, you were out late.
I was busy.
August 10th.
When a friend learned he was tutoring,
he asked Narukami Yu to help out at the daycare center.
He had no way of knowing that these simple tasks
would lead to new hardships.
You broke it!
Did not!
What's going on?
Yuuta broke my Neo Featherman robot!
It's not broken! Lemme see it!
Let go!
Stop it! Don't fight—
I'm terribly sorry.
I can't fix this.
I'm truly sorry.
Well, I expect you to compensate for the toy.
Very well.
But I didn't break it.
I'm truly very sorry.
Um, I'll pay for it.
You see, I broke it.
How much was it?
Welcome home!
Should I warm your dinner up?
Sorry, but I already ate.
You did?
Oh, Nanako. Have you heard of Neo Featherman?
Yeah, everyone loves him.
I see. Heroes these days are something else, aren't they?
Thus began Narukami Yu's struggles
in a harsh world that revolved around Loveline and Neo Featherman.
Damn you, Neo Featherman!
Hey, Dojima!
We may have solved the case, but watch the booze!
Hey, Yu!
Y-Yes?
If it isn't a chick, what's keeping you out so late?
Actually...
A fox asked me to pick up a part-time job.
It's put me through a lot.
Since when were you such a tease?
Yu, that was a riot!
What's wrong?
I know that feeling.
August 16th.
Narukami Yu is once again assaulted by some unforeseen trouble.
Do this and—
Don't lie!
I'm not lying!
You shouldn't fight!
But Yuuta said he saw Loveline!
I did! I really saw her!
But Loveline only exists in the TV.
Hey!
Ouch!
Ow!
What was that for?!
Hey, cut it out!
Geez, what should I do?
Don't fight!
I'm dying!
It's like Hell in here!
Bye-bye!
Hey, Teddie! What are you doing out here?
Why is everyone here?
Huh? Why aren't you saying anything?
I should act like Teddie and hightail it out of here.
What a weird bear.
I-I'm not a suspicious bear.
Doesn't his voice sound off?
And he's all stiff.
Yeah, it doesn't seem natural.
He's normally more, uh, hyperactive.
Like how he randomly rolls around.
Oops!
Now!
W-Why'd he run from us?
He's the culprit!
Teddie's got it bear-y tough.
August 17th.
After learning the hardships of labor and the life of Teddie,
Narukami Yu has grown a little more mature.
But there's no time for rest.
It's really cloudy today.
Earning money is hard.
Thief! Someone catch him!
Ma'am!
She apparently hit her head when the thief pushed her.
But it doesn't look serious.
There's no need to worry.
That's great.
But my, aren't you cute?
Why don't we go hit the town?
No, I've got work.
Too bad.
Sorry, but I'll be out late, so you two can eat without me.
Okay, I understand.
Big Bro said he'd be home late.
Just what is he up to?
That's...
Hey, mister...
Is school fun?
Sure, it's fun.
Really? It isn't fun for me at all.
I'm always surrounded by idiots.
August 18th.
Summer vacation is halfway over,
and his interactions with the people around him are beginning to change.
Oh, you're that boy from yesterday.
Oh, good morning.
Were you coming to see me?
No, I'm going to visit that elderly woman.
Is this for me?
It's for an in-patient.
You're surprisingly forward.
I don't have a problem with that.
What?
Huh? Where are we going?
Don't you worry about that.
I can't stand being a nurse!
The old farts are bossy, and the men leer at me!
That must be hard.
And everyone always leaves me as soon as they recover.
But it's good they get discharged.
Maybe I should quit my job.
What would you do then?
I don't know!
Say, let's put that aside.
Did you know there's going to be a festival?
Why don't we go together?
I'm going with my friends.
You can breeze through it with them.
I'll give you my number, so give me a call.
I smell like alcohol.
You're from the daycare center.
Oh, I found a bug!
Hey, let's go over there.
Okay!
You see, Yuuta isn't really my son.
He's from my husband's old marriage.
You don't say.
That's why I'm still so unsure of how to act around him.
I'm sure he hates me, too.
Oh, Mommy!
See ya!
Okay...
I wish I could just relax by myself.
Oh my!
Aren't you...
Yeah!
Watch your step.
Thank you.
I'm going to be moving soon.
This town holds too many memories of my late husband for me to stay.
Isn't it lovely?
My husband gave it to me a long time ago.
But I don't need it anymore.
My love for him had dried up there at the end.
So there's no point in hanging onto those old memories.
I'm glad I met you here in the end.
You're the spitting image of my husband in his younger years.
Tune your TV in to "Tanaka's Amazing Commodities"!
Enjoy the show!
Here's our big commodity for the day!
It's the legendary fishing pole, the "Explosive Fishing Set"!
This indomitable fishing pole will never break!
With this, you'll only need one line and hook!
Call now, and we'll throw in a set of fishing gear—
That's it!
Excuse me!
I've got a delivery here.
Thank you.
Big Bro...
I'm heading out!
Narukami Yu disappears into the light, but his hot summer vacation is still under way!
August 20th.
Narukami Yu's summer vacation is finally reaching its climax.
You've got some major bags under your eyes!
Wow! I wanna eat some shaved ice!
You okay?
I've been busy.
Isn't Nanako with you?
Um, all of them!
My uncle's bringing her later.
I'll be right back.
Huh? Okay.
Excuse me!
I had a feeling we'd run into each other again.
I want to give you something.
That's my... But how?
I'll get it this time!
Persona!
Doesn't it mean a lot to you?
You seemed really sad after you threw it.
So, here.
Oh my...
I was so happy when my husband gave this to me that I couldn't see his face through all my tears.
I... I truly loved my husband, huh?
Shu!
M-Mister!
What's that?
Isn't it...
I don't want any fireworks!
Everyone in class was promising they'd watch the fireworks together.
But no one invited me to come along.
Everyone's just jealous of me because they're stupid!
So now, no one gets fireworks!
I'm going to ruin their nights, too!
Shu...
I have something for you.
What is it?
Happy birthday, Shu.
How'd you know?
I noticed a picture in your room that said today is your birthday.
But why did you choose this?
It's a game you can't play by yourself.
You'll have to ask someone to play with you.
But everyone else is so stupid.
Does it matter?
It's fun goofing off with everyone.
Oh, my stomach!
That's lame.
That's what you get for eating so much shaved ice!
Mister, I stole the fireworks.
Let's give them back!
Huh?
I'll apologize with you later.
For now, just leave it to me!
Look what you did!
What? It wasn't my fault!
You did that on purpose!
Now, now, Yuu...
Give it a rest, really!
If there's something wrong with the bitch, then there's something wrong with the pup.
Well, this is about what I'd expect from a failure of a mother.
But I...
Why, you little brat!
Yuu!
Hey! Wake up!
What in the...
What happened?
Mister...
I-It wasn't my fault!
She's bleeding bad!
Mister, help her. Please help her!
Of course!
My, I didn't think he'd actually call.
Hello?
I need your help!
Huh?
She's bleeding from the head.
Please tell me what to do!
Wait. What's going on?
Please!
You got it.
First, bandage the wound with a long piece of material.
Something long...
Huh? What are you doing?
Ebi, I need to borrow this.
Huh?
What next?
Try to keep it cool.
I-I'm sorry, but we're out of ice.
What's wrong, Narukami?
Well, you see...
Oh!
Here's your delivery.
Mom!
Yuu?
It looks like she'll be okay.
Yeah, thanks.
Mom! Mom!
Hey, Daddy. I want that big one!
Ah!
Mister!
I made it in time!
Thanks. You're the first person to do anything like this for me.
Wow! It's Loveline!
See? Told ya she's real!
I wasn't lying!
Right, Mom?
You sure weren't, Yuu.
Instructor, thank you so much.
I think I might've lost sight of what really matters.
What's that?
Saving lives truly is wonderful, isn't it?
I can't believe I forgot something so simple.
But you helped me remember. Thank you.
Thank you for helping me regain my memories.
I shall cherish them this time.
Of course. Take care.
Hello? Amagi?
Huh? I'm with her right now.
It's Yukiko.
Hello?
Huh? Really?
It's hard to walk in this.
Nanako, you're so adorable!
You look great.
You're still eating?
Why not?
Don't blame me if you get sick again.
Sorry we took so long!
It took a while getting everyone dressed.
Lookin' good! Lookin' real good!
Everyone's so pretty!
Hey! Thanks for taking care of her.
Uncle, didn't you have work?
Yeah, but I dumped it on Adachi.
I can't pass up on the festival!
They gave me some cotton candy!
Really?
Now then, why don't we go hit up a shooting booth?
Sounds good!
Well, you guys have fun.
Big Bro, I'll see you later.
It's nighttime at a festival.
A couple leans up against each other.
Unaccustomed to wearing a yukata, it spills open.
Oh, summer...
What's with the sudden monologue?
It's only natural for us to pair off and enjoy the sights!
Yeah! I agree with Teddie!
Great! I've already decided who I'm going with.
Hey, not so fast!
I'll pair up with Chie, Yuki, and Rise.
That's not how you pair up!
As such, I'll go with all you ladies.
Dude, we suck. We really suck!
That is the full account of Narukami Yu's summer vacation.
Mr. Fox!
Wai—
It's my Loveline!
Thank you, Mr. Fox!
Thank you...
And that's case closed!
I can't wait to go on this school trip!
It's the boy detective.
Doodly-doo!
You'd better leave this kid alone!
That's so embarrassing!
Where's that voice coming from?
What are the king's orders?
Next up!